<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>BBC Nitro programmes feed - nitro</title>
    <link>http://mermade.github.io/feeds</link>
    <description>Unofficial BBC iPlayer feeds via the Nitro API</description>
    <webMaster>mike.ralphson@gmail.com (Mike Ralphsonno)</webMaster>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 23:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    <generator>bbcparse by Mermade Software</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Meg Rosoff - Jonathan Unleashed: Omnibus : Episode 1 - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b071c693</link>
      <description>In New York, fresh from college, can Jonathan Trefoil navigate the responsibilities of adulthood? Read by Rhashan Stone.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b071c68x</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 15:08:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Jonathan Unleashed : Episode 10 - Episode 10</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0717n9x</link>
      <description>Final instalment of the ten part abridgement of the new novel by Meg Rosoff, read by Rhashan Stone.

Unemployed, single and starting to despair, Jonathan has asked his former colleague Greeley to help him find a new direction for his life. Accompanied by Dante the collie and Sissy the spaniel, the four leave New York behind for a weekend spent deep in the forest. While there, Jonathan receives a series of texts that suggest all is not lost with Dr Clare.


Read by Rhashan Stone.

Written by Meg Rosoff.

Abridged by David Jackson Young.

Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0717n9r</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imagining Chekhov : Chekhov&apos;s Telescope - 26/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0717lrz</link>
      <description>A set of three stories, commissioned specially for Radio 4. Alison MacLeod explores the life and work of one of the finest short story writers of them all - Anton Pavlovich Chekhov.

Episode Two:
Chekhov and his lover - the actress Olga Knipper - take a holiday in Yalta, unaware that a news reporter is stalking their every move.

A note on the letters between Chekhov and Olga.
These are fictional composites of the writer&apos;s own words and Chekhov&apos;s actual letters from the volume Dear Writer, Dear Actress: The Love Letters of Anton Chekhov and Olga Knipper, translated by Jean Benedetti.

Alison MacLeod lives in Brighton. She was shortlisted for the BBC National Short Story Award in 2011 and her stories Solo, A Capella and In Praise Of Radical Fish have featured in previous Radio 4 series. Her works include The Changeling and The Wave Theory of Angels. Her novel, Unexploded, was long-listed for the Man Booker Prize and was broadcast as Book At Bedtime. Alison is Professor of Contemporary Fiction at the University of Chichester.

Reader: Peter Firth
Producer: Jeremy Osborne

A Sweet Talk production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0717lh3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Jonathan Unleashed : Episode 9 - Episode 9</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0717j26</link>
      <description>The new novel by Meg Rosoff, author of the bestselling &quot;How I Live Now&quot;. It&apos;s the story of a young man, Jonathan Trefoil who - assisted by his canine companions Dante the collie and Sissy the spaniel - is struggling to navigate the responsibilities of adulthood and the demands of his new life in New York.

Cured of his speech problems after being jilted at the altar by Julie, Jonathan is ready to return to work at Comrade - despite the misgivings of his friend Max and work colleague Greeley.


Read by Rhashan Stone.

Written by Meg Rosoff.

Abridged by David Jackson Young.

Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0717hwy</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 00:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Jonathan Unleashed : Episode 8 - Episode 8</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0717cq2</link>
      <description>The new novel by Meg Rosoff, read by Rhashan Stone. It&apos;s the story of a young man, Jonathan Trefoil who - aided by his canine companions Dante the collie and Sissy the spaniel - is struggling to navigate the responsibilities of adulthood and the demands of his new life in New York.

Jonathan and Julie&apos;s wedding day arrives. With her employer Bridal-360 organising everything (including live-streaming the ceremony to an audience of 100,000 viewers) and Jonathan still unable to form coherent sentences, what could possibly go wrong?


Read by Rhashan Stone.

Written by Meg Rosoff.

Abridged by David Jackson Young.

Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0717cf4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 00:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Jonathan Unleashed : Episode 7 - Episode 7</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b07178gg</link>
      <description>The new novel by Meg Rosoff, read by Rhashan Stone. It&apos;s the story of a young man, Jonathan Trefoil who - aided by his canine companions Dante the collie and Sissy the spaniel - is struggling to navigate the responsibilities of adulthood and the demands of his new life in New York.

After his breakdown at work, Jonathan wakes up in hospital to discover that he&apos;s unable to form coherent sentences, generating random text instead. Neurologists are baffled by his case and there&apos;s little they can do except recommend strict bed rest. Julie is left responsible for the dogs and, during one of their walks, has a fateful meeting with a tall dark stranger.


Read by Rhashan Stone.

Written by Meg Rosoff.

Abridged by David Jackson Young.

Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b07177sm</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Jonathan Unleashed : Episode 6 - Episode 6</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b07145y0</link>
      <description>Rhashan Stone continues reading from the new novel by Meg Rosoff, her first for adults, Jonathan Unleashed. The story of a young man, Jonathan Trefoil who - aided by his canine companions Dante the collie and Sissy the spaniel - is struggling to navigate the responsibilities of adulthood and the demands of his new life in New York.

Jonathan&apos;s stress levels are going through the roof. Increasingly unhappy at work, he has hastily accepted his girlfriend Julie&apos;s commercially sensible proposal: to get married and have everything paid for by her employer, Bridal-360, in exchange for an eight page spread in the magazine and permission to live-stream the ceremony online to an audience of 100,000. What could possibly go wrong?


Read by Rhashan Stone.

Written by Meg Rosoff.

Abridged by David Jackson Young.

Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b07145fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 17:37:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 13 : Climate Change - 22/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b07142ls</link>
      <description>Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined by guests Dara O Briain, Professor Tony Ryan and Dr Gabrielle Walker to discuss the ever-hot topic of climate change. They take a forensic look at the evidence that the climate is indeed changing, how we know that we are responsible, and what can be done to stop it. The scientific willing may be there, but is the political will finally catching up?</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b071421g</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 12:58:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short Story: Say Yes by Tobias Wolff - 21/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0713x9k</link>
      <description>A couple are washing up after their evening meal. A casual conversation reveals a startling difference between them. How well do we know those who we love and live with?

Written by Tobias Wolff
Read by Henry Goodman

Produced by Jill Waters
A Waters Company production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0713wz7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 13:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stories : The Easter Lilies - 21/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0713pqt</link>
      <description>Julia McKenzie reads Jane Gardam&apos;s classic story in which an elderly spinster dreams of adorning her suburban church with the wild lilies of her time in Malta, with unexpected results...
Reader: Julia McKenzie is a distinguished stage and screen actor, with two Olivier awards and Tony and BAFTA nominations. Her most recent TV roles include Miss Marple in the Agatha Christie TV series, and her film roles include Notes on a Scandal and Shirley Valentine.
Abridger: Justine Willett
Producer: Justine Willett
Born in 1928, Jane Gardam she did not publish her first book until she was in her 40s, but has become one of the most prolific novelists of her generation, with 25 books published over the past 30 years and a number of prestigious prizes to her name (she&apos;s twice winner of the Whitbread, and has been shortlisted for both the Booker and Orange prizes). Her novels include Old Filth, Last Friends, God on the Rocks and The Hollow Land. She&apos;s been called &apos;the laureate of the demise of the British Empire&apos;, for her poignant and witty portrayals of the end of the era of British imperial adventures.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0713pfk</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 01:15:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Woolf - Orlando: Omnibus : Episode 2 - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b070pcsn</link>
      <description>Orlando, the Tudor time travelling adventurer, is preoccupied by the penalties and privileges of womanhood. Read by Amanda Hale.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b070pcsl</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 16:35:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Jonathan Unleashed : Episode 5 - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b070hxsx</link>
      <description>Rhashan Stone reads the new novel by bestselling author Meg Rosoff.

Moving to New York fresh from college, Jonathan Trefoil&apos;s new life as an adult with grown-up responsibilities is not going quite as planned. Although he knows it&apos;s a terrible idea, he has hastily accepted his girlfriend Julie&apos;s marriage proposal: she works for a wedding magazine and they&apos;ve offered to pay for everything in return for live-streaming the ceremony and running a four-page spread in the next issue. Soon, the stress of his personal life spills over into his work and the only thing keeping him sane is the companionship of his brother&apos;s dogs, Dante and Sissy.


Written by Meg Rosoff.

Read by Rhashan Stone.

Abridged by David Jackson Young.

Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b070hxrt</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 01:12:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imagining Chekhov : Woman with a Little Pug - 19/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b070hxsd</link>
      <description>A set of three stories, commissioned specially for Radio 4. Alison MacLeod explores the life and work of one of the finest short story writers of them all - Anton Pavlovich Chekhov.

Episode One:
In this playful reworking of Chekhov&apos;s classic tale &apos;The Lady With A Little Dog&apos;, a philanderer encounters a woman in a Brighton hotel. But they can&apos;t help thinking they&apos;ve met each other somewhere before.

Alison MacLeod lives in Brighton. She was shortlisted for the BBC National Short Story Award in 2011 and her stories Solo, A Capella and In Praise Of Radical Fish have featured in previous Radio 4 series. Her works include The Changeling and The Wave Theory of Angels. Her novel, Unexploded, was long-listed for the Man Booker Prize and was broadcast as Book At Bedtime. Alison is Professor of Contemporary Fiction at the University of Chichester.

Reader: Peter Firth
Producer: Jeremy Osborne

A Sweet Talk production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b070hvjz</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 01:12:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Jonathan Unleashed : Episode 4 - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b070hnsc</link>
      <description>Bestselling author Meg Rosoff&apos;s new novel, set in New York, read by Rhashan Stone.

Jonathan Trefoil has arrived in New York ready for his life to begin. He&apos;s found an apartment and is temporarily in charge of his brother&apos;s dogs (Dante, a Border Collie, and Sissy, a Spaniel) while his brother is working in Dubai. His best friend Max has got him a job at Comrade, a marketing company run by one of their school friends. He has a smart girlfriend, Julie, who has just joined him in the city. Life is good... isn&apos;t it?

Julie&apos;s unexpected proposition, and his hasty acceptance, leaves Jonathan reeling. A visit to his parents doesn&apos;t quite go as planned and, back at work, as things unravel further, leading office manager Greeley to step in with some wise advice.


Written by Meg Rosoff.

Read by Rhashan Stone.

Abridged by David Jackson Young.

Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b070hnq0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 01:15:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Jonathan Unleashed : Episode 3 - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b070fn24</link>
      <description>The new novel by bestselling author Meg Rosoff, read by Rhashan Stone.

Jonathan Trefoil has arrived in New York fresh from college and ready for his life to begin. He&apos;s found himself an apartment and he&apos;s temporarily in charge of his brother&apos;s dogs (Dante, a Border Collie, and Sissy, a Spaniel) while his brother is working in Dubai. His best friend Max has landed him a job at Comrade, a marketing company run by one of their school friends. He has a smart girlfriend, Julie, who has just joined him. Life is good... isn&apos;t it?

Greeley, Comrade&apos;s new Office Manager, brings a brighter, healthier vibe to Jonathan&apos;s working life - even encouraging him to bring the dogs into work. But just as Jonathan begins to feel that he&apos;s getting on top of his new life, Julie floors him with a commercially sensible proposition.


Written by Meg Rosoff.

Read by Rhashan Stone.

Abridged by David Jackson Young.

Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b070fn0k</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 01:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Jonathan Unleashed : Episode 2 - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b070dr3m</link>
      <description>Rhashan Stone reads the new novel by Meg Rosoff, author of the bestselling &quot;How I Live Now&quot;.

Set in New York, the novel follows graphic designer Jonathan Trefoil as he navigates big city life as a fully-fledged adult. Aided by canine companions Dante the collie and Sissy the spaniel - who&apos;ve been left in his charge by his brother James - Jonathan wishes there was a book he could read (&quot;How To Be A Person&quot;) that would help him cope with his new responsibilities.

Increasingly worn down by his mind-numbing job in a marketing company, the one bright spot on Jonathan&apos;s horizon is the imminent arrival of his girlfriend Julie. But what will she make of the tiny apartment he&apos;s found? And how will she get on with the dogs?


Read by Rhashan Stone.

Written by Meg Rosoff.

Abridged by David Jackson Young.

Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b070dr34</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Jonathan Unleashed : Episode 1 - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b070d5sw</link>
      <description>The first adult novel by Meg Rosoff, author of the bestselling Young Adult novel &quot;How I Live Now&quot;.

Jonathan Trefoil has arrived in New York from college and is ready for his life to begin. He&apos;s found himself an apartment and he&apos;s temporarily in charge of his brother&apos;s dogs (Dante, a Border Collie, and Sissy, a Spaniel) while his brother is working in Dubai. His best friend Max gets him a job at Comrade, a marketing company run by one of their school friends. He has a smart girlfriend, Julie, who will join him once she&apos;s found work. Life seems good.

But it isn&apos;t really, he&apos;s lost; a dreamer floundering. His creativity is stifled by the mind-numbing work at Comrade: thinking up pithy ways to sell a budget office supplies company&apos;s wares, which they always reject in favour of tried and tested slogans &quot;Pens: 3 for 2&quot;. He holds onto his sanity by writing a graphic novel &quot;The New York Inferno&quot; in which a Border Collie spirit guide accompanies a young poet through the nine circles of the New York underworld.

Things gradually come to a head when Julie secures a job in her company&apos;s New York office and the different, unhappy strands of Jonathan&apos;s life begin to slowly unravel.


Read by Rhashan Stone.

Written by Meg Rosoff.

Abridged by David Jackson Young.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b070d5sp</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 00:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 13 : Maths of Love and Sex - 15/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b070cxyb</link>
      <description>Robin Ince and Brian Cox get romantic (although unfortunately not with each other) as they discuss the mathematics of love and the statistics of sex. They are joined on stage by comedian and former maths student Paul Foot, mathematician Hannah Fry and statistician Professor Sir David Speigelhalter, as they discover whether a knowledge of numbers can help you in the affairs of the heart? Can a maths algorithm help you find your perfect mate at a party and what do the statistics tell us about what happens after the party, if you do! They find out whether mathematicians are more successful at dating than comedians, and whether a rational, scientific approach to love and life long happiness is really the answer.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b070cxwr</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 11:37:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shorts : Scottish Shorts : Still Life - 14/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b070cgkr</link>
      <description>By Margaret Morton Kirk
Artist Jack lives quietly on a remote Scottish island until a chance meeting with a tourist changes everything.
Read by Melody Grove
Producer Eilidh McCreadie

Margaret Morton Kirk is a writer from Inverness. Her short stories have achieved success in a number of competitions and she is currently working on a crime novel set in her home town.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b070cfty</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 18:35:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stories : The Pig Boy - 14/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0707y3j</link>
      <description>Jessica Raine reads Jane Gardam&apos;s classic story in which a young wife is thrilled to be rejoining her husband in Hong Kong, still under the British. But all too soon she finds herself looking for authenticity and excitement...

Reader: Jessica Raine is best known for her role as Jenny in the TV drama Call the Midwife. Other recent TV credits include Jane Boleyn in Wolf Hall, and Tuppence Beresford in Partners in Crime. 
Producer: Justine Willett
Abridger: Julian Wilkinson
Writer: Born in 1928, Jane Gardam she did not publish her first book until she was in her 40s, but has become one of the most prolific novelists of her generation, with 25 books published over the past 30 years and a number of prestigious prizes to her name (she&apos;s twice winner of the Whitbread, and has been shortlisted for both the Booker and Orange prizes). Her novels include Old Filth, Last Friends, God on the Rocks and The Hollow Land. She&apos;s been called &apos;the laureate of the demise of the British Empire&apos;, for her poignant and witty portrayals of the end of the era of British imperial adventures.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0707xjw</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:06:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Woolf - Orlando: Omnibus : Episode 1 - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06zzmjz</link>
      <description>Orlando, a young nobleman in Tudor England, embarks on a tumultuous journey spanning five centuries. Read by Amanda Hale.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zzmjw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 16:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Orlando : The Present - Episode 10</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06zvdlv</link>
      <description>In Virginia Woolf&apos;s sumptuous novel the present catches up with Orlando&apos;s extraordinarily lengthy past. The reader is Amanda Hale.

Abridged by Richard Hamilton
Produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zvcx5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Deliveries : Second Class, Signed For - 12/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06zvbwq</link>
      <description>A series of stories about some rather Special Deliveries, commissioned to mark the anniversary of the Royal Mail 500 years after Cardinal Wolsey appointed the first Master of the Posts in 1516. 

In Lucy Gannon&apos;s story a curiously behaving dog leads a postman to make a rather unexpected delivery, while Kate Woodward takes us to the French court, and the tradition of royal gift exchange. In our final episode Colin Carberry&apos;s story is about Laura, a young wife and mother who is making some tough decisions by way of the Royal Mail.

Reader ..... Jodie Whittaker
Writer ..... Colin Carberry
Producer ..... Jenny Thompson.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zvbsr</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Orlando : The Most Influential Critic of the Victorian Age - Episode 9</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06zv3xk</link>
      <description>Orlando arrives at an ending and a new beginning.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zv3bs</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 01:23:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Orlando : Marmaduke Bonthrop Shelmerdine, Esquire - Episode 8</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06ztw0p</link>
      <description>In Virginia Woolf&apos;s boisterous novel the oppressive nineteenth century dawns, and an extraordinary encounter takes place out on the moor. The reader is Amanda Hale.

Abridged by Richard Hamilton
Produced by Elizabeth Allard

Virginia Woolf&apos;s high-spirited novel, read by Amanda Hale.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zttw3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 00:11:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Orlando : Society&apos;s Seductions - Episode 7</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06zs231</link>
      <description>In Virigina Woolf&apos;s boisterous novel Orlando finds herself in eighteenth century England where she is seduced by London society, and intoxicated by the words of the poets. The reader is Amanda Hale.

Abridged by Richard Hamilton
Produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zs1kk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 01:14:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Orlando : The Enamoured Lady - Episode 6</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06zqq9q</link>
      <description>In Virginia Woolf&apos;s high spirited novel her eponymous heroine is preoccupied by the penalties and privileges of womanhood. First off all a sojourn in the mountains of Broussa leads to further reflections on love and nature.

The reader is Amanda Hale.
Abridged by Richard Hamilton
Produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zqq3q</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostail agus Sgeulachdan Eile : Sgeulachdan &apos;Ball-coise&apos; agus &apos;Cricket&apos; - 08/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06zqpj1</link>
      <description>Rugadh agus thogadh an sgrìobhadair, an neach-teagaisg agus an fhìor Niseach, Tormod Caimbeul, Tormod a&apos; Bhocsair ann an Dail bho Dheas, Leòdhas. Sgrìobh e grunn leabhraichean do dh&apos; inbhich leithid Deireadh an Fhoghair, An Druim bho Thuath, Shrapnel agus An Naidheachd bhon Taigh. Do chloinn bha Uilleam Ban agus an Iolaire, A&apos; Chailleach Chrubach, Dòmhnall mac Dhòmhnaill mac Dhòmhnaill, agus Cathal Garg is a Hearach. Chruinnich e cuideachd rannan do chloinn agus chàich anns a&apos; leabhar àlainn Air do Bhonnagan a Ghaoil agus dh&apos;eadar-theangaich e samhail Tè Bheag a&apos; Ghruffalo is leabhraichean Katie Morag do chloinn.

Ann a 1992, agus e air fhastadh mar sgrìobhadair aig Roinn an Fhoghlaim de Chomhairle nan Eilean, chaidh cruinneachadh de na sgeulachdan aige, Hostail agus Sgeulachdan Eile, fhoillseachadh do dheugairean, sgeulachdan stèidhichte air a làithean-sgoile ann a Steòrnabhagh sna 50an. Chaidh an craoladh an toiseach ann a 1993 agus &apos;s iomadh facal a thog iad am measg shean is òg. Gur math as fhiach èisteachd riutha uair eile!

Bhàsaich Tormod sa Chèitean 2015 aig aois 72. Chaidh an cruinneachadh mu dheireadh de na sgeulachdan goirid aige, Sgeulachdan sa Chiaradh, fhoillseachadh le Acair san Dàmhair.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zqphq</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:10:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 13 : What Is Reality? - 08/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06zqpcg</link>
      <description>What is Reality?

Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined by US superstar neuroscientist David Eagleman, Professor Sophie Scott and comedian Bridget Christie to ask what is reality? Is our sense of the world around us a completely personal experience and a construct of our brains? How can we ever know whether what one person perceives is exactly the same as what another person perceives. Is your sense of the world around you an illusion constructed by this extraordinary organ, the brain, that has no direct access to the outside world that it is helping you to understand.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zqpc7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shorts : Scottish Shorts : Everyone&apos;s the Same Inside - 07/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06zqk36</link>
      <description>By Wayne Price
Guilt, laughter and death come to mind as a man recalls his family&apos;s long connection to a reclusive outsider.
Read by Steven McNicoll
Producer Eilidh McCreadie

Author Wayne Price was born in south Wales and has lived and worked in Scotland since 1987. He is an award-winning fiction and poetry writer and has twice been a finalist for the Manchester International Poetry Prize. He teaches at the University of Aberdeen and his debut novel, &apos;Mercy Seat&apos; was published in 2015.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zqjhh</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 00:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stories : Hetty Sleeping - 07/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06zq9y7</link>
      <description>Hattie Morahan reads Jane Gardam&apos;s classic short story in which a mother is forced to question the sacrifices she&apos;s made, when an ex-lover and former teacher at the Slade turns up on a family holiday in Connemara.

Reader: Hattie Morahan is an acclaimed television, film, and stage actress. Her notable film roles include Alice in The Bletchley Circle and Ann in Mr Holmes; he recent TV roles include the doomed mother in Sadie&apos;s Jones&apos; The Outcast, and neighbour Jane in Outnumbered.
Producer: Justine Willett
Abridger: Julian Wilkinson
Writer: Born in 1928, Jane Gardam she did not publish her first book until she was in her 40s, but has become one of the most prolific novelists of her generation, with 25 books published over the past 30 years and a number of prestigious prizes to her name (she&apos;s twice winner of the Whitbread, and has been shortlisted for both the Booker and Orange prizes). Her novels include Old Filth, Last Friends, God on the Rocks and The Hollow Land. She&apos;s been called &apos;the laureate of the demise of the British Empire&apos;, for her poignant and witty portrayals of the end of the era of British imperial adventures.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zq9y1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 01:31:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Orlando : A Transformation - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06zcmjq</link>
      <description>In Virginia Woolf&apos;s sumptuous novel her eponymous hero has been sent to opulent Constantinople by King Charles I to serve as Ambassador Extraordinary. Whilst there he undergoes a miraculous transformation. The reader is Amanda Hale.

Abridged by Richard Hamilton
Produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06zcm58</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 01:26:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Orlando : An Admirer - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06z9kdv</link>
      <description>In Virginia Woolf&apos;s celebrated novel Orlando turns his mind to his noble ancestry and an archduchess demands his attention. Read by Amanda Hale.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06z9kdp</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 01:17:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Orlando : A Lampooning - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06z9bg8</link>
      <description>In Virginia Woolf&apos;s spirited novel Orlando aspires to the life of a poet and is compelled to extend an invitation to an admired writer. Read by Amanda Hale.

Abridged by Richard Hamilton
Produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06z9b91</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 00:08:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Orlando : The Muscovite Princess - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06z98rc</link>
      <description>In Virginia Woolf&apos;s boisterous novel Orlando&apos;s adventures continue when a beguiling Muscovite princess skates into view on the frozen Thames at the court of James I. The reader is Amanda Hale

Abridger: Richard Hamilton
Producer: Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06z98qz</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 00:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automobile Club of Egypt: Omnibus : Episode 2 - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06z8kwx</link>
      <description>Mitsy meets the King of Egypt. But the outcome does not please her father. Alaa Al Aswany&apos;s novel is read by Raad Rawi, Amir El-Masry and Emerald O&apos;Hanrahan.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06z8kwv</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 12:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Deliveries : Zarafa - 05/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06z5jmf</link>
      <description>A series of stories about some rather Special Deliveries, commissioned to mark the anniversary of the Royal Mail 500 years after Cardinal Wolsey appointed the first Master of the Posts in 1516. 

In Lucy Gannon&apos;s story a curiously behaving dog leads a postman to make a rather unexpected delivery, while Kate Woodward takes us to the French court, and the tradition of royal gift exchange. In our final episode Colin Carberry&apos;s story is about Laura, a young wife and mother who is making some tough decisions by way of the Royal Mail.


Reader ..... Adrian Lukis
Writer ..... Kate Woodward
Producer ..... Jenny Thompson.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06z5h0g</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 01:26:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostail agus Sgeulachdan Eile : Sgeulachd - &apos;Trom an t-eallach an Gaol&apos; - 01/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06z2rbj</link>
      <description>Rugadh agus thogadh an sgrìobhadair, an neach-teagaisg agus an fhìor Niseach, Tormod Caimbeul, Tormod a&apos; Bhocsair ann an Dail bho Dheas, Leòdhas. Sgrìobh e grunn leabhraichean do dh&apos; inbhich leithid Deireadh an Fhoghair, An Druim bho Thuath, Shrapnel agus An Naidheachd bhon Taigh. Do chloinn bha Uilleam Ban agus an Iolaire, A&apos; Chailleach Chrubach, Dòmhnall mac Dhòmhnaill mac Dhòmhnaill, agus Cathal Garg is a Hearach. Chruinnich e cuideachd rannan do chloinn agus chàich anns a&apos; leabhar àlainn Air do Bhonnagan a Ghaoil agus dh&apos;eadar-theangaich e samhail Tè Bheag a&apos; Ghruffalo is leabhraichean Katie Morag do chloinn.
Ann a 1992, agus e air fhastadh mar sgrìobhadair aig Roinn an Fhoghlaim de Chomhairle nan Eilean, chaidh cruinneachadh de na sgeulachdan aige, Hostail agus Sgeulachdan Eile, fhoillseachadh do dheugairean, sgeulachdan stèidhichte air a làithean-sgoile ann a Steòrnabhagh sna 50an. Chaidh an craoladh an toiseach ann a 1993 agus &apos;s iomadh facal a thog iad am measg shean is òg. Gur math as fhiach èisteachd riutha uair eile!
Bhàsaich Tormod sa Chèitean 2015 aig aois 72. Chaidh an cruinneachadh mu dheireadh de na sgeulachdan goirid aige, Sgeulachdan sa Chiaradh, fhoillseachadh le Acair san Dàmhair.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06z2qrh</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:10:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Orlando : Boyhood - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06z2flh</link>
      <description>In Virginia Woolf&apos;s boisterous adventure her hero, Orlando, embarks on a tumultuous journey spanning five centuries.

Orlando, &quot;the longest and most charming love letter in literature&quot; was intended for and inspired by Vita Sackville-West and her noble roots. Along with the eponymous hero&apos;s adventuring through the ages, Woolf explores what it means to write and the all important question of gender - as relevant and resonant today as it was in the 1920s when she wrote this high spirited novel.


Orlando, is a young nobleman in Tudor England when we first encounter him and he writes the first lines of his poem, The Oak Tree, a poem that he keeps about him as he travels through time. Swept along by his adventures we next find him as he falls in love for the first time with a beautiful Russian princess on the frozen Thames at the court of James I. A desire to write leads to a disastrous meeting with a much admired poet before, under Charles 1, he becomes the king&apos;s charismatic ambassador in Constantinople. A dramatic transformation takes place in this opulent city and Orlando continues his adventures as a woman. Returning to eighteenth century London, the life of the poet continues to call, but later the restrictions placed upon Orlando by the Victorian era are impossible to bear. Glimmers of new possibilities arrive with the twentieth century and the promise of fulfilment through love and writing.

Reader: Amanda Hale
Abridger: Richard Hamilton
Producer: Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06z2ctl</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:05:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 13 : Invisible Universe - 01/02/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06z2851</link>
      <description>Brian Cox and Robin Ince transport the cage of infinite proportions to the Manchester Museum of Science and Industry. They are joined on stage by impressionist Jon Culshaw and astrophysicists Sarah Bridle and Tim O&apos;Brien as they look up at the sky to discover that everything we see only accounts for 5% of the entire universe. So what is the rest of the universe made of? What are these mysterious elements known as Dark Matter and Dark Energy and would their discovery mean a complete re-writing of the laws of physics as we know them?

Producer: Alexandra Feachem.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06z2611</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:05:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shorts : Scottish Shorts : The Mary Tree - 31/01/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06z1zfg</link>
      <description>By Linda Cracknell
A boy visiting his mother in hospital meets a strange character with intriguing tales of a lost landmark.
Read by Robert Jack
Producer Eilidh McCreadie

Author Linda Cracknell has been inspired by her work as writer-in-residence at The Royal Hospital for Sick Children in Edinburgh. The hospital moves to a new location in 2017.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06z1x8x</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 01:19:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stories : The Tribute - 31/01/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06z1zd9</link>
      <description>Miriam Margolyes reads Jane Gardam&apos;s classic short story in which three former colonial ladies gather to pay tribute to their dutiful old nanny, who did so much for them during the halcyon days overseas. When it transpires that she has left something for all of them, they are not at all surprised - until the gift arrives...

Reader: Miriam Margolyes is a is a veteran of stage and screen, a BAFTA Award-winning actor, whose roles have included: Yentl, Little Shop of Horrors, Scorsese&apos;s The Age of Innocence, Cold Comfort Farm and the Harry Potter film series.
Producer: Justine Willett
Abridger: Julian Wilkinson
Writer: Born in 1928, Jane Gardam she did not publish her first book until she was in her 40s, but has become one of the most prolific novelists of her generation, with 25 books published over the past 30 years and a number of prestigious prizes to her name (she&apos;s twice winner of the Whitbread, and has been shortlisted for both the Booker and Orange prizes). Her novels include Old Filth, Last Friends, God on the Rocks and The Hollow Land. She&apos;s been called &apos;the laureate of the demise of the British Empire&apos;, for her poignant and witty portrayals of the end of the era of British imperial adventures.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06z1mbv</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 01:17:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : The Automobile Club of Egypt : Episode 10 - Episode 10</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06ys5tg</link>
      <description>Once a respected landowner, Abd el-Aziz Gaafar has fallen into penury and has moved his family to Cairo. He is forced into menial work at the Automobile Club, a refuge of colonial luxury and privilege for its European members.

A vibrant and moving story of a family swept up by social unrest in post-War Cairo, written by Alaa Al Aswany, the internationally best-selling author of The Yacoubian Building and Chicago.

Episode 10:
Events build to a violent climax after which nothing will be the same again.


Read by Raad Rawi, Amir El-Masry and Emerald O&apos;Hanrahan
Translated by Russell Harris
Abridged by Jeremy Osborne

Produced by Karen Rose
A Sweet Talk production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06ys5tb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 01:13:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Deliveries : How Lovely on the Mountain - 29/01/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06yfyp9</link>
      <description>A series of stories about some rather Special Deliveries, commissioned to mark the anniversary of the Royal Mail 500 years after Cardinal Wolsey appointed the first Master of the Posts in 1516. 

In Lucy Gannon&apos;s story a curiously behaving dog leads a postman to make a rather unexpected delivery, while Kate Woodward takes us to the French court, and the tradition of royal gift exchange. In our final episode Colin Carberry&apos;s story is about Laura, a young wife and mother who is making some tough decisions by way of the Royal Mail.

Reader ..... Kevin Whately
Writer ..... Lucy Gannon
Producer ..... Heather Larmour.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06yfwlx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 01:13:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 13 : What is Race? - 25/01/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06ybg84</link>
      <description>Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined on stage by comedian Shappi Khorsandi, science broadcaster Adam Rutherford and evolutionary geneticist Mark Thomas. They look at the thorny issue of race, and whether there is a scientific definition for the concept of race. Do our genes reveal racial differences, and if so do they tell us anything about our evolutionary history? They also look at the results of their own personal DNA tests...so which panellist is a little bit neanderthal and which one has a genetic history firmly rooted in the North!

Producer: Alexandra Feachem.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06ybg1y</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 17:29:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 13 : Artificial Intelligence - 18/01/2016</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06wcsng</link>
      <description>Artificial Intelligence

Brian Cox and Robin Ince return for a new series of their award winning science/comedy show. Tonight the infinite monkey&apos;s are joined on stage by comedian Jo Brand, neuroscientist Anil Seth, and robotics expert Alan Winfield to discuss Artificial Intelligence. How close are we to creating a truly intelligent machine, how do we define intelligence anyway, and what are the moral and ethical issues that the development of intelligent machines might bring?

Producer: Alexandra Feachem.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06wcrnx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 13:32:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : The Infinite Monkey Cage Christmas Special - 25/12/2015</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b06scz8s</link>
      <description>The Science of Doctor Who
Brian Cox and Robin Ince celebrate the festive season with a look at the science of Doctor Who. Swapping the infinite cage for the Tardis, they are joined on stage by comedian Ross Noble, Professor Fay Dowker, Oscar winning special FX director Paul Franklin, author and Doctor Who writer Simon Guerrier and the Very Reverend Victor Stock. They discuss the real science of time travel, the tardis and why wormholes are inaccurately named (according to Ross!).</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b06scys2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 00:07:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 12 : Forensic Science - Episode 6</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b064yglg</link>
      <description>A Forensic look at Forensics

No dead strawberries this week, but plenty of dead bodies, as Brian Cox and Robin Ince take a gruesome look at the science of death and some of the more unusual ways that forensic scientists are able to look for and gather clues and evidence. From insects that can be used to give a precise time of death, to the unusual field of forensic botany, It&apos;s not just DNA evidence that can be used to pinpoint someone to the scene of a crime. They are joined on stage by Professor Sue Black from the University of Dundee, Dr Mark Spencer, a forensic botanist at the Natural History Museum and comedian Rufus Hound.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b064yf0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 13:49:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 12 : Speed - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b063zx1g</link>
      <description>The Need for Speed

The Monkey Cage returns from its tour of the USA, as Brian Cox and Robin Ince take to the stage of the BBC Radio Theatre to look at the science of speed. They are joined by comedian and former motoring correspondent for the Daily Telegraph, Alexei Sayle, Land Speed Record Holder Andy Green and Professor Danielle George from the University of Manchester. They&apos;ll be looking at the engineering challenges of creating the fastest vehicle on the planet, and whether the limits to human speed are engineering or the laws of physics themselves.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b063zwp0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 12:50:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 12 : The Infinite Monkey Cage USA Tour: San Francisco - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0639jp8</link>
      <description>Brian Cox and Robin Ince take to the stage in San Francisco for the last of their USA specials. They talk alien visitations, UFOs and other close encounters with astronomer Dr Seth Shostack, NASA scientist Dr Carolyn Porco, and comedians Greg Proops and Paul Provenza.

Producer: Alexandra Feachem.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0639j0q</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 23:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 12 : The Infinite Monkey Cage USA Tour: Chicago - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b062jy94</link>
      <description>Fossil Records and other Archaeological Hits.

Brian Cox and Robin Ince take to the stage in Chicago, Illinois, to discuss fossil records and evolution. They are joined on stage by host of NPR&apos;s &quot;Wait Wait Don&apos;t Tell Me&quot; Peter Sagal, comedian and Saturday Night Live alumnus Julia Sweeney, palaeontologist Paul Sereno and evolutionary biologist Jerry Coyne.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b062jwx6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 16:34:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 12 : The Infinite Monkey Cage USA Tour: Los Angeles - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b061qht1</link>
      <description>Science Goes to Hollywood: Science Fact V Science Fiction

Brian Cox and Robin Ince continue their tour of the USA, as they take to the stage in LA. They are joined by cosmologist and science advisor on movies such as Thor and Tron Legacy, Sean Carroll, comedian Joe Rogan, The Simpsons&apos; writer and Executive Producer of Futurama, David X Cohen, and Eric Idle. They ask why so many movies now seem to employ a science advisor, whether scientific accuracy is really important when you are watching a film about a mythical norse god and whether science fact can actually be far more interesting than science fiction.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b061qd80</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 15:56:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 12 : The Infinite Monkey Cage USA Tour: New York - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b060zddz</link>
      <description>The Infinite Monkey Cage USA Tour: New York

The Infinite Monkeys return for a new series, the first of which will see them head to the USA for their first live tour. This week Brian Cox and Robin Ince can be found on stage in New York asking the question, Is Science a Force for Good Or Evil? They are joined on stage by Bill Nye the Science Guy, cosmologist Janna Levin, actor Tim Daly and comedian Lisa Lampanelli.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b060zd64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 23:03:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 11 : Serendipity - Episode 6</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b053721m</link>
      <description>Serendipity in Science

Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined on stage by comedian Lee Mack, science author and journalist Simon Singh and chemist Professor Andrea Sella to look at how many of our biggest science discoveries seem to have come about by accident. From Viagra to Pyrex to the discovery of the Cosmic Background Microwave Radiation, the earliest remnant of the big bang, they all owe their discovery to a healthy dose of luck and accident as scientists stumbled across them in the course of looking for something else. So are these discoveries just luck, are they still deserving of Nobel prizes and scientific glory, or is serendipity and an open scientific mind key to exploring and understanding our universe?</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b05371sc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 16:23:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 11 : What Is the Point of Plants? - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b052hptj</link>
      <description>What&apos;s the Point of Plants?

Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined on stage by plant biologist Professor Jane Langdale, physicist Professor Jim Al-Khalili and comedian and former horticulture student Ed Byrne to ask, &quot;what&apos;s the point of plants?&quot;. How would the evolution of life on our planet have differed without plants, and what would our planet look like today? Most crucially that seemingly dull but necessary process of photosynthesis that we all learned about in school, is in fact one of the most important processes in our universe, and as usual it seems, the physicists are trying to take credit for it. Could there be a quantum explanation for how this amazing reaction works, and if so, are plants in fact the perfect quantum computers?</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b052hpns</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 13:46:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 11 : When Quantum Goes Woo - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b051ryq8</link>
      <description>When Quantum Goes Woo

Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined on stage by Bad Science author, Ben Goldacre, Professor of Particle Physics at Manchester University, Jeff Forshaw, and comedian Sara Pascoe. They&apos;ll be looking at why quantum physics, in particular, seems to attract some of the more fringe elements of pseudoscience and alternative medicine, and whether there is anything about the frankly weird quantum behaviour of particles, like the ability to seemingly be in two places at once, that really can be applied to the human condition. When spiritual healers and gurus talk about our own quantum energy and the power of quantum healing, is it simply a metaphor, or is there more to this esoteric branch of science that we could all learn from?</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b051rxb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 00:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 11 : Solar System - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b050zy3x</link>
      <description>Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined by comedian Jo Brand, planetary scientist Professor Monica Grady and NASA scientist Dr Carolyn Porco as they discuss some of the most exciting and technically ambitious explorations of our solar system. They&apos;ll be looking at the Rosetta mission that has, for the first time, landed a probe on a comet, and the Cassini-Huygens mission which is bringing us extraordinary information about Saturn and its moons, and what these explorations of the far reaches of our solar system might tell us about our own planet.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b050zt9y</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2015 00:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 11 : Fierce Creatures - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b05061zb</link>
      <description>Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined on stage by naturalist Steve Backshall, zoologist Lucy Cooke and comedian Andy Hamilton as they battle it out to decide which creature wins the title of earth&apos;s most deadly. The panel reveal their own brave encounters with a host of venomous, toxic and just downright aggressive beasts, including the bullet ant, rated the most painful stinging insect on the planet, deadly tree frogs and snakes, sharks, scorpions and hippos. They ask whether our seemingly innate fear of snakes and spiders is justified, and whether the deadliest creature on the planet is in fact a human being.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b05061mx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 00:00:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 11 : Deception - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b04yfsst</link>
      <description>Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined on stage by author and journalist David Aaronovitch, psychologist Professor Richard Wiseman and neuroscientist Professor Sophie Scott as they tackle the science of deception. They&apos;ll be asking why we seem to be so good at telling lies, but not very good at spotting them, and why being good liars could be the secret to our success as a social animal. They will also be carrying out their own act of deception on the monkey cage audience. They reveal the results of an experiment to test the idea of subliminal advertising, carried out by David Aaronovitch for the Radio 4 documentary, &quot;Can You Spot the Hidden Message&quot; . Will they manage to secretly persuade a section of the theatre audience to pick one type of soft drink over another by secretly flashing the name of a certain brand on a screen? All will be revealed.

Producer: Alexandra Feachem.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b04yfrhs</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2015 00:00:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : The Infinite Monkey Cage Christmas Special - 25/12/2014</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b04vjb5y</link>
      <description>Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined by Brian Blessed, astronaut Chris Hadfield, bible scholar Professor Francesca Stavrakopoulou and the Reverend Richard Coles for a very special festive edition of the show. They&apos;ll be taking their own unique look at the Christmas story and the history of the bible and asking whether the christmas story and your view of humanity changes once you&apos;ve look back at earth from the heavens themselves.

Producer : Alexandra Feachem.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b04vjb2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 23:36:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 10 : Irrationality - Episode 6</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b04d1lwx</link>
      <description>Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined by comedians Josie Long and Paul Foot, psychologist Richard Wiseman and neuroscientist Stuart Ritchie to ask &quot;is irrationality genetic?&quot;. The second of two programmes recorded at the Edinburgh Festival.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b04d1lr2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 12:13:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 10 : Before the Big Bang - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b04cbbld</link>
      <description>Brian Cox and Robin Ince transport the cage of infinite proportions, for the first of 2 programmes from the Edinburgh Festival. They are joined on stage by cosmologists Carlos Frenk and Faye Dowker and actor and comedian Ben Miller and comedian and fellow physics PhD alumnus Richard Vranch.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b04dm6wq</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 14:44:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 10 : Can Science Save Us? - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b04bn0gp</link>
      <description>Can Science Save Us?

Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined on stage by Stephen Fry, Eric Idle, chemist and Pro-Vice-Chancellor of Sheffield University, Professor Tony Ryan, and University of London solar scientist, Dr Lucie Green, as they ask: &quot;can science save us?&quot; They&apos;ll be looking at some of the fantastic ideas at the very forefront of science and technology that are being looked at to help in tackling some of the biggest challenges facing our planet, from climate change, to feeding our ever expanding global population.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b04cb12h</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 11:28:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 10 : Does Science Need War? - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b049y9pj</link>
      <description>Does Science Need War?

Brian Cox and Robin Ince are joined on stage by comedian Katy Brand, science writer Philip Ball and medic, author and broadcaster Kevin Fong. They&apos;ll be asking whether scientific progress needs the pressures and casualties of war to drive it, or whether some of our biggest scientific breakthroughs, that have resulted from periods of conflict, would have happened anyway? It&apos;s a serious topic, but never fear, on the way the intergalactic battles faced in Star Wars, and why only the French could come up with onions as a cure for burns, are all equally seriously investigated.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b04bsrq4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 11:25:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 10 : Are Humans Uniquely Unique? - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b049699x</link>
      <description>Are humans uniquely unique?

Robin Ince and Brian Cox are joined on stage by human and non-human ape experts Keith Jensen, Katie Slocombe and Ross Noble to ask whether humans are truly unique amongst animal species. They&apos;ll be looking at why studying our nearest relative, the chimpanzee, could reveal clues as to how humans evolved some of the traits that make us stand out, such as language, culture and truly altruistic cooperation, or whether these are traits that are now being uncovered in our primate cousins. They&apos;ll also be revealing why a chimpanzee could be classified as far more rational than its human counterpart.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b04b6qxg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 23:00:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infinite Monkey Cage : Series 10 : Numbers Numbers Everywhere - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b048jmy9</link>
      <description>Numbers, Numbers everywhere...

The Infinite Monkey Cage is back for a new series of witty, irreverent science chat. Over the coming six weeks, presenters Brian Cox and Robin Ince will be joined on stage by scientists and some well known science enthusiasts including Stephen Fry, Ross Noble, Katy Brand and Ben Miller to discuss a range of topics, from what makes us uniquely human, to whether irrationality is, in fact, genetic.

In the first episode of the new series, Brian and Robin are joined by comedian and former maths undergraduate Dave Gorman, maths enthusiast and author Alex Bellos and number theorist Dr Vicky Neale to look at the joy to be found in numbers. Although many people fear maths and will admit to dreading any task that requires even basic skills of numeracy, the truth is that numbers really are everywhere and our relationship with them can, at times, be oddly emotional. Why do so many people have a favourite number, for example, and why is it most often the number 7? 7 is of course a prime number - a favourite amongst mathematicians and non-mathematicians alike, although seemingly for different reasons. Could it be however, as the panel discuss, that the reasons are not so very different, and that we are all closet mathematicians at heart?</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b049jppq</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 13:27:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet David Sedaris : Series 4 : English Lesson; Understanding Understanding Owls - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03mclqh</link>
      <description>One of the world&apos;s funniest storytellers is back on BBC Radio 4 doing what he does best. 

This week, he considers his native tongue as if it were a foreign language in &quot;English Lesson&quot; and the trouble that taxidermy can bring in &quot;Understanding Understanding Owls&quot;.

Producer: Steve Doherty
A Giddy Goat production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b03mclgw</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:42:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet David Sedaris : Series 4 : Company Man; Diary Extracts - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03m3nty</link>
      <description>One of the world&apos;s funniest storytellers is back on BBC Radio 4 doing what he does best.

This week, the pros and cons of being grown up enough to have a guest room in &quot;Company Man&quot;, and some more extracts from his hilarious diary, which he has kept nightly for over 30 years. 

Producer: Steve Doherty
A Giddy Goat production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b03m3npg</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 01:18:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet David Sedaris : Series 4 : #2 to Go; Innocents Abroad - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03lnprh</link>
      <description>One of the world&apos;s funniest storytellers is back on BBC Radio 4 doing what he does best. 

This week, in &quot;#2 to Go&quot;, a trip to China does not work out well for David - especially on the food front. 

The second story is called &quot;Innocents Abroad&quot; and tackles the tricky tightrope of &quot;going native&quot; when learning a foreign language.

Producer: Steve Doherty
A Giddy Goat production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b03lnpr5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 01:15:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saki : The She Wolf - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03kvd4v</link>
      <description>by Hector Hugh Munro, better known by his pen name Saki.

A mischievous story in which Saki&apos;s regular character Clovis springs an elaborate trick on fellow guests at a house party. A playful satire on Edwardian society with a streak of the ludicrous.

Read by Maureen Beattie
Produced by Allegra McIlroy.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b03kvccv</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 17:22:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet David Sedaris : Series 4 : Repeat After Me - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03kp2kh</link>
      <description>One of the world&apos;s funniest storytellers is back on BBC Radio 4 doing what he does best.

This week, a story dealing with the guilt he sometimes feels as a result of writing stories about his family in &quot;Repeat After Me&quot; and some more extracts from his hilarious diary. 

Producer: Steve Doherty
A Giddy Goat production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b03kp2k8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 01:49:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet David Sedaris : Series 4 : The Happy Place; The Shadow of Your Smile - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03jysr6</link>
      <description>One of the world&apos;s funniest storytellers is back on BBC Radio 4 doing what he does best.

There are two stories, this week: &quot;The Happy Place&quot;, dealing with the ups and downs of a colonoscopy; and &quot;The Shadow of Your Smile&quot;, about how the right lighting can make us all look good. 



Producer: Steve Doherty
A Giddy Goat production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b03jys2w</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 01:26:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gillian Tindall - The Great Eastern Adventure - 23/08/2013</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b038qbkn</link>
      <description>Aunt Susie and Uncle Trevor&apos;s long-planned trip proved momentous, but didn&apos;t go at all according to plan. Read by Jean Rogers.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b038qbk7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 15:39:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feminine Mystiques : Mink - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b037jn8q</link>
      <description>By Marina Warner
Read by Emma Fielding


Fifty years since the first publication of Betty Friedan&apos;s seminal feminist work The Feminine Mystique, Radio 4 has commissioned three leading writers to celebrate her influence in new short stories exploring the contemporary feminist landscape.

Emma Fielding reads the first story in this series, by award winning writer and mythographer Marina Warner. Just as some of Angela Carter&apos;s short stories from The Bloody Chamber were first published in high fashion magazine Vogue, and Carter&apos;s retelling of fable and myth turned on the original meaning of &apos;glamour&apos; as a spell, Marina Warner explores feminine mystique through a housewife in the 1950s who weaves hope and freedom into her longing for a mink coat.

Marina Warner has written novels, short stories and non-fiction centering around women and the imagery and iconography they conjure for more than thirty years.

The other writers in the series are British-Sierra Leonean novelist Aminatta Forna, winner of the Commonwealth Writers Prize and judge of the Man Booker International Prize, with a surreal and wryly humourous contemporary story read by Doon MacKichan, and Sarah Hall, one of Granta&apos;s Best Young British Novelists 2013, who brings us a story set in a dystopian near future, read by Francesca Dymond.



Producer: Allegra McIlroy.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b037jmzp</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 00:32:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nabokov&apos;s Christmas - 25/12/2012</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01pfy5p</link>
      <description>by Vladimir Nabokov.


An intensely moving short story about a father mourning the death of his son. On Christmas Eve, a grieving father moves around the family home gathering together some of his son&apos;s effects. This leads him to discover things that he did not know about his beloved son and also to find something among his belongings that will renew his will to live. 


Vladimir Nabokov was born in St. Petersburg in 1899, the eldest son of an aristocratic family. Nabokov is arguably most famous for his 1955 novel LOLITA. 



Read by Robert Glenister.


Produced by Gaynor Macfarlane.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01pfxlh</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 18:33:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Ben&apos;s Chimes : Maintaining Big Ben - Episode 7</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01nt4q1</link>
      <description>Made for 4 Extra. Archive recordings and a new poem by Ian McMillan pay tribute to the familiar tone of the chimes of &apos;Great Uncle Ben&apos;.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01nt42s</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 11:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twenty Minutes : Incident on Lake Geneva - 06/09/2012</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01mf8q6</link>
      <description>&quot;On the banks of Lake Geneva, close to the small Swiss resort of Villeneuve, a fisherman who had rowed into the lake one summer night in the year 1918, noticed a strange object in the middle of the water...&quot;

In Stefan Zweig&apos;s famous story, translated by Anthea Bell, a man clings to driftwood out on the lake. When he&apos;s brought ashore the townsfolk react to his arrival in different ways. Just who is he, this stranger, talking in an odd language?

Reader Dermot Crowley

Producer Duncan Minshull.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01mf8ht</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 12:09:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Taylor Short Stories : The Blush - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01kksrg</link>
      <description>Acclaimed short story writer and novelist Elizabeth Taylor was known for her witty and powerful explorations of the bitter frustrations and passions which lurk beneath the civilised veneer of middle class life.

In The Blush, the peaceful but empty existence of a childless housewife implodes when she realises that the influence of her cleaning lady is far more wide-reaching than she had ever imagined.


Produced by Amanda Hargreaves.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01kksmb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2013 00:52:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedy Greats : Overseas - 07/07/2012</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01kjsg3</link>
      <description>Captain Barry Cryer welcomes you aboard a special edition of Comedy Greats showcasing a selection of the BBC&apos;s hit comedy shows that were adapted for listeners overseas. 

During the 1950s to 1970s, a surprising number of series were either edited, rescripted or remade. 

Barry reveals bits that never made it out of Blighty to enable shows to be better understood abroad. 

Featuring: 
The Clitheroe Kid - Another Mother for Ossie. From November 1965 
The Navy Lark - Going Dutch. From November 1959 
The Men From the Ministry - Birds of a Feather. Re-recording from 1980. 
Hancock&apos;s Half Hour - The New Secretary. Re-recorded in November 1958. 
Round the Horne - The Man With the Golden Thunderball. Re-recorded July 1966 with an edited version of the original script. 
I&apos;m Sorry, I&apos;ll Read That Again - series 3 (10/13). Re-recording from 1966. 

Produced by Kerry Reece for BBC Radio 4 Extra.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01kjqzg</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 09:56:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Food of Love : The Lovely Miss What&apos;s-Her-Face - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01kjlhr</link>
      <description>In this series of monologues exploring the link between food and memory, poignant domestic dramas gradually unfold through the preparation of a special recipe. 

In this story, &apos;The Lovely Miss What&apos;s-Her-Face&apos; by Kevin Barry, winner of the 2012 Sunday Times short story award, an insurance clerk of a certain age recreates the exotic spaghetti bolognese he cooked for the lass in the typing pool, on his last romantic date - some 30 years before...

Kevin Barry&apos;s first novel, &apos;City of Bohane&apos;, was shortlisted for the Costa first novel award, and a previous short story collection, &apos;There Are Little Kingdoms&apos;, won the Rooney prize for Irish Literature.

Read by: David Schofield
Producer: Justine Willett.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01kjlbl</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 01:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twenty Minutes : Lizzie&apos;s Tiger - 29/06/2012</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01jz48f</link>
      <description>&apos;The tiger walked up and down, up and down; it walked up and down like Satan walking about the world and it burned. It burned so brightly, she was scorched.&apos;

It is 1864, and the Borden family are living in a poor way in River Fall, Massachusetts, when, one day, the circus comes to town. Defying her grave undertaker father, the squat, square infant, Lizzie Borden, who will one day take an axe to her parents, slips out illicitly to the circus. Dazzled by the bawdy sights and sounds around her, the four-year-old girl finds herself in the animal enclosure. A magnificent tiger is pacing up and down his tiny cage, when, for one extraordinary moment, their eyes meet, and Lizzie&apos;s destiny is sealed...

Angela Carter died 20 years ago, and is remembered as one of the great literary figures of the 20th century. &apos;Lizzie&apos;s Tiger&apos;, one of the last pieces she wrote, was originally commissioned for BBC Radio 3, and published posthumously in a collection, American Ghosts and Old World Wonders. It is one of her many short stories in which she reimagines the lives of certain historical figures; in this case the young life of the notorious Lizzie Borden, who would one day be tried for murdering parents.

Reader: Debora Weston
Abridged and produced by: Justine Willett.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01jz47x</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 10:10:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Beginner&apos;s Goodbye : Episode 10 - Episode 10</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01hl4hn</link>
      <description>By Anne Tyler.


Read by William Hope.


Pulitzer Prize-winning author Anne Tyler&apos;s novel is the story of Baltimore publisher Aaron Woollcott&apos;s recovery from the death of his wife, Dorothy.


After a number of visits from Dorothy - who appeared to Aaron in reassuringly solid and non-supernatural form - the pair have made their peace. Aaron is finally ready to move on to the next stage of his life and finds love in an expected quarter.


Abridged by Robin Brooks.


Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01hl4gc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2012 00:18:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Beginner&apos;s Goodbye : Episode 9 - Episode 9</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01hl2bb</link>
      <description>By Anne Tyler.


Read by William Hope.


Anne Tyler&apos;s novel is the story of Baltimore publisher Aaron Woollcott&apos;s recovery from the death of his wife, Dorothy, who was killed when a tree fell on their home.


Aaron is waiting patiently for Dorothy&apos;s next appearance. He&apos;s staying with his sister while repairs are being done to the house, but her relationship with Gil is becoming more serious it&apos;s starting to dawn on him that he may have outstayed his welcome.


Abridged by Robin Brooks.


Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01hl1t6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 09:00:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Beginner&apos;s Goodbye : Episode 8 - Episode 8</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01hkz31</link>
      <description>By Anne Tyler.


Read by William Hope.


The new novel by the Pulitzer Prize-winning author Anne Tyler is the story of Baltimore publisher Aaron Woollcott&apos;s recovery from the death of his wife, who was killed when a tree fell on their home.


Aaron has been distracted from his grief by a series of reassuringly solid, and ordinary, visits from his dead wife. 


Abridged by Robin Brooks.


Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01hkyss</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 08:55:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Beginner&apos;s Goodbye : Episode 7 - Episode 7</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01hjs1p</link>
      <description>By Anne Tyler.


Read by William Hope.


The new novel by the Pulitzer Prize-winning author Anne Tyler is the story of Baltimore publisher Aaron Woollcott&apos;s recovery from the death of his wife, who was killed when a tree fell on their home.


Emerging slowly from his grief, Aaron is spending a lot of time thinking about the early days of his marriage.


Abridged by Robin Brooks.


Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01hjry4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 00:12:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Beginner&apos;s Goodbye : Episode 6 - Episode 6</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01hjq7g</link>
      <description>By Anne Tyler.


Read by William Hope.


The new novel by the Pulitzer Prize-winning author Anne Tyler is the simple yet profound story of one man&apos;s recovery from the death of his wife.


While family and friends fuss around him, widower Aaron Woolcott ploughs on, busying himself with work at the family firm, a small publisher with a successful line in &quot;Beginner&apos;s Guides&quot; to every stage and aspect of life (from &quot;The Beginner&apos;s Spice Rack&quot;, to &quot;...Kitchen Remodelling&quot;, to &quot;...Funerals&quot;). 


Surprised by the different stages of his grief, and watching his sister begin a relationship with his builder, Aaron recalls the first few tentative dates he had with his late wife, Dorothy.


Abridged by Robin Brooks.


Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01hjq3j</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 00:09:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Beginner&apos;s Goodbye : Episode 5 - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01hdg0t</link>
      <description>By Anne Tyler.


Read by William Hope.


The new novel by the Pulitzer Prize-winning author Anne Tyler is the simple yet profound story of one man&apos;s recovery from the death of his wife.


Slowly, as the repairs to his home start to take shape, Aaron&apos;s grief begins to ease. 


Abridged by Robin Brooks.


Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01hdg03</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 00:11:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Beginner&apos;s Goodbye : Episode 4 - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01hdfzl</link>
      <description>By Anne Tyler.


Read by William Hope.


The new novel by the Pulitzer Prize-winning author Anne Tyler is the simple yet profound story of one man&apos;s recovery from the death of his wife.


Arriving home from work to find water pouring through the roof of his house, Aaron is forced to call in a builder and face up to the extent of the tree&apos;s damage.


Abridged by Robin Brooks.


Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01hdfz8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 00:13:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Beginner&apos;s Goodbye : Episode 3 - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01hdfvp</link>
      <description>By Anne Tyler.


Read by William Hope.


The new novel by the Pulitzer Prize-winning author Anne Tyler is the simple yet profound story of one man&apos;s recovery from the death of his wife.


In the aftermath of the freak accident that killed his wife, Aaron seeks to regain some semblance of normality by going back to live in the wreckage of their home. Throwing himself into his work, as editor at his family&apos;s small vanity press in Baltimore, he tries to evade the sympathetic efforts of his colleagues and neighbours.


Abridged by Robin Brooks.


Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01hdftz</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 00:11:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Beginner&apos;s Goodbye : Episode 2 - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01hc9st</link>
      <description>By Anne Tyler.


Read by William Hope.


The new novel by the Pulitzer Prize-winning author Anne Tyler is the simple yet profound story of one man&apos;s recovery from the death of his wife. 


In this episode, Aaron Woolcott, editor at his family&apos;s small publishing house in Baltimore, reveals how a freak accident claimed the life of his wife Dorothy.


Abridged by Robin Brooks.


Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01hc9rp</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 00:12:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Beginner&apos;s Goodbye : Episode 1 - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01h646r</link>
      <description>By Anne Tyler.


Read by William Hope.


The new novel by the Pulitzer Prize-winning author Anne Tyler is the simple yet profound story of one man&apos;s recovery from the death of his wife.


While family and friends fuss around him, widower Aaron Woolcott ploughs on. He busies himself with work at the family firm, a small publisher with a successful line in &quot;Beginner&apos;s Guides&quot; to every stage and aspect of life (from &quot;The Beginner&apos;s Spice Rack&quot;, to &quot;...Kitchen Remodelling&quot;, to &quot;...Funerals&quot;). Then, at the point when Aaron thinks he can&apos;t go on, Dorothy, his wife, begins to appear to him in reassuringly solid form.


Abridged by Robin Brooks.


Produced by Kirsteen Cameron.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01h645x</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 05:42:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leap Year Tales : Excepting February - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01cwwlj</link>
      <description>Three stories to mark the Leap Year.

&apos;Excepting February&apos; by Alan Spence.

February&apos;s extra day threatens to cause technical meltdown in Scotland&apos;s granite city, but meanwhile may give love another chance for one man.

Read by John Buick.

Produced by Patricia Hitchcock

Alan Spence is an award-winning poet and playwright, novelist and short story writer. His awards include the McVitie Prize (Scottish Writer of the Year). He is Professor in Creative Writing at the University of Aberdeen where he also founded and directed the annual WORD Festival from 1999-2011. His most recent novel, &apos;The Pure Land&apos;, was translated into 19 languages. His latest book is &apos;Morning Glory&apos;, a poetry collection with illustrations by Elizabeth Blackadder.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01cwvyt</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:42:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under the Skin : Eyebrows, by Kavita Bhanot - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01cvdds</link>
      <description>Under the Skin is a celebration of the second ever South Asian Literature Festival, which is staged in London and across the United Kingdom. 

The relationship between the English language, its literary tradition and writers from South Asia has become an exciting and enduring part of British literary life. The Festival celebrates writers from South Asia and British Asian writing, equally, reflecting the diversity of themes, subjects and literary forms that constitute South Asian writing in 2012. 

Under the Skin features three stories by British Asian writers. Kavita Bhanot&apos;s Eyebrows introduces us to three generations of women seen through the eyes of Jaya on her weekend visits to her grandmother. 

Lyndam Gregory, Deni Francis and Najma Khan are the readers.


Producer: David Roper
A Heavy Entertainment production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01cvddn</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 01:08:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leap Year Tales : February Alone - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01cks4t</link>
      <description>Three stories to mark the Leap Year.

&apos;February Alone&apos; by Ruth Thomas.

An intended romantic lunch goes strangely awry. Will a gift of lingerie help save the hour?

Read by Melody Grove.

Produced by Patricia Hitchcock.

Ruth Thomas is the author of three short story collections and a novel. Her first collection, &apos;Sea Monster Tattoo&apos;, was shortlisted for the John Llewellyn Rhys Award and her novel, &apos;Things to Make and Mend&apos; was winner of Good Housekeeping&apos;s &apos;Most Entertaining Read&apos; Award. She has also received a Scottish Arts Council Book Award and has had work shortlisted for the VS Pritchett Prize. Her second novel is due out next year and she is also at work on a new short story collection.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01ckrv4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 00:46:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under the Skin : Another Life, by Resma Ruia - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01cj384</link>
      <description>Under the Skin is a celebration of the second ever South Asian Literature Festival, which is staged in London and across the United Kingdom. The relationship between the English language, its literary tradition and writers from South Asia has become an exciting and enduring part of British literary life. The Festival celebrates writers from South Asia and British Asian writing, equally, reflecting the diversity of themes, subjects and literary forms that constitute South Asian writing in 2012. 

Under the Skin features three stories by British Asian writers. Resma Ruia&apos;s Another Life focuses on the restlessness of an Asian businessman who visited Manchester as a young man on his way to America - but never left. 

Lyndam Gregory, Deni Francis and Najma Khan are the readers.


Producer: David Roper
A Heavy Entertainment production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01cj2lt</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 01:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leap Year Tales : Aw Wrong - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01c7x4m</link>
      <description>Three stories that mark Leap Year.

&apos;Aw Wrong&apos; by Laura Marney.

Facing the imminent birth of their first child, a couple take steps to try to influence the course of nature.

Read by Gabriel Quigley.

Produced by Patricia Hitchcock

Laura Marney is a writer of fiction and drama. She is the author of four novels: &apos;No Wonder I Take a Drink&apos;, Nobody Loves a Ginger Baby&apos;, &apos;Only Strange People go to Church&apos; and most recently, &apos;My Best Friend has Issues&apos;. She is currently working on a new novel provisionally entitled &apos;Snorkelling in a Burkha&apos;.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01c7x23</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 00:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under the Skin : Correspondence - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01c6s87</link>
      <description>Under the Skin is a celebration of the second ever South Asian Literature Festival, which was staged in London and across the United Kingdom in October. The relationship between the English language, its literary tradition and writers from South Asia has become an exciting and enduring part of British literary life. 

The Festival celebrated writers from South Asia and British Asian writing, equally, reflecting the diversity of themes, subjects and literary forms that constitute South Asian writing in 2011. 

Under the Skin features two original stories and one adapted from the collection Too Asian, Not Asian Enough which was published to coincide with the festival. NSR Khan&apos;s story Correspondence is a touching and witty account of a Pakistani father coming to terms with the life of his British Asian daughter. 

Under the Skin starts with Deni Francis, Lyndam Gregory and Najma Khan reading a story in letters between a father and daughter. 


Producer: David Roper
A Heavy Entertainment production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01c6rx3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 01:10:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Country : Episode 3 - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01bwd37</link>
      <description>Neil Ansell is living in a very remote part of the Welsh countryside, on his own, with no electricity, gas or water, and only the wildlife around him for company. He survives the gales but has to face another storm - his own vulnerability. Read by Matthew Gravelle.

Abridged by Willa King. 
Directed by Emma Bodger
A BBC Cymru Wales Production.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01bwbvd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 01:33:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Country : Episode 2 - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01bkhjl</link>
      <description>Neil Ansell is living in a very remote part of the Welsh countryside, on his own, with no electricity, gas or water, and only the wildlife around him for company. The winters are particularly hard, but he revels in the isolation and tranquillity. Read by Matthew Gravelle.

Abridged by Willa King
Directed by Emma Bodger
A BBC Cymru Wales Production.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01bkgg3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 01:18:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Country : Episode 1 - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01b8xcb</link>
      <description>Neil Ansell is in search of solitude. He takes up home in a dilapidated cottage in a very remote part of the Welsh countryside, on his own, with no electricity, gas or water. He has only wildlife around him for company as he makes the cottage habitable. Read by Matthew Gravelle.

Abridged by Willa King
Directed by Emma Bodger
A BBC Cymru Wales Production.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b01b8x5m</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 01:23:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twenty Minutes : From Buddenbrooks - 22/08/2011</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b013m2cy</link>
      <description>&quot;An enormous brick-red, boiled ham appeared, strewn with crumbs and served with a sour brown onion sauce, and so many vegetables that the company could have satisfied their appetites from that one dish. 

Lebrecht Kroger undertook the carving, and skillfully cut the succulent slices, with his elbows slightly elevated and his two long forefingers laid out along the back of the knife and fork. With the ham went the Frau Consul&apos;s celebrated &quot; Russian jam&quot; - a pungent fruit conserve flavoured with spirits.&quot;

From Thomas Mann&apos;s classic German novel, set in the mid 1800s, comes this evocation of a sumptuous dinner party, presided over by old Johann Buddenbrooks and his son, the Consul. Father and his cronies stand for the Old Order, whilst the Consul sees change in the wind. Whatever, the family are close and much merriment is had, even when Dr Grabow is called to deal with a pressing case of... well, what exactly?


Read by Adrian Scarborough.
Translated by HT Lowe-Porter.
Producer Duncan Minshull.

First broadcast in August 2011.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b013m219</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 09:26:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twenty Minutes : The Modern Soul - 04/08/2011</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b012x14m</link>
      <description>Katherine Mansfield&apos;s story is written from the perspective of a witty female who befriends a buffoonish professor. The guests at a German pension decide to take part in a concert. Fraulein Sonia performs a theatrical dance and Herr Professor plays his trombone. The narrator describes this performance with quiet amusement and cynicism. 

Katherine Mansfield applies her characteristic wit to this story, The Modern Soul, first published in the collection In a German Pension. 

Read by Sophie Thompson
Produced by Lucy Collingwood.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b012x11l</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 08:55:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Reading : The Foxes Come at Night : Gondolas - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b012l1yv</link>
      <description>Now in his eightieth year, Cees Nooteboom is one of Holland&apos;s leading and most respected authors, a writer of both novels and travel books and a consummate short story writer. The Foxes Come at Night, his recent collection, has won the 2010 Gouden Uil - the most prestigious literary award in Flanders and is now published in English.
The collection is set in the cities and islands of the Mediterranean, territory Nooteboom knows well. The stories are linked by their meditations on memory and age, on love won and lost and on the fragments of life treasured in a photograph or a detail.
In &apos;Gondolas&apos; a fine art dealer finds the past stirred by a photograph taken on the same Venetian canal bank forty years ago. In &apos;Thunderstorm&apos; a couple&apos;s own fissures are reflected in a horrific moment on a beach. And in &apos;Late September&apos; a woman waits on a windblown Spanish cafe terrace before the inevitable conclusion to her lonely day.
Written with haunting attention to detail and pitch perfect prose, sensitively translated by Ina Rilke, these stories show one of the European masters of the genre at his best.
Reader Ian McDiarmid
Abridger Sally Marmion
Producer Di Speirs.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b012l1xy</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 23:00:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Key&apos;s Suspended Sentence - 05/07/2011</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0128pyh</link>
      <description>Truths universally acknowledged. Clocks striking thirteen. Bests and worsts of times. A truly great opening line can make a novel iconic. But what makes these famous first sentences sing to us?

Last year, Perrier award-winning comedian and poet Tim Key chased down the meaning of Nikolai Gogol&apos;s enigmatic short story &quot;The Overcoat&quot;, in a feature that garnered some of the most prestigious awards in European radio - winning the EBU&apos;s Ake Blomstrom Prize, and being nominated for the Prix Italia and Prix Marulic.

Now, another chance to hear his first radio &apos;documentary&apos; (sort of), originally aired in 2011, as he tries to sleuth out what makes a great literary opening line, with the help of author Joe Dunthorne, comedian and novelist Mark Watson, and literary critics Maureen Freely and John Sutherland. You see, Tim&apos;s just desperate to write his first novel - it&apos;s in him, just waiting, waiting to be unleashed. If only he could think of a good beginning...

Fresh from his acclaimed stage show &quot;Masterslut&quot; and regular spots on Charlie Brooker&apos;s &quot;Newswipe&quot; and Steve Coogan&apos;s &quot;Mid-Morning Matters With Alan Partridge&quot;, Tim&apos;s on a mission to pen the ultimate opening line: one that will knock your socks off, hook you in, blow you away (he&apos;ll sort out the rest later, yeah?).

As he slowly crafts his one-sentence magnum opus, Tim taps into the minds of some of Britain&apos;s top literary talents to find out what a first line should and shouldn&apos;t do, and the hours of sweat and toil enshrined in those crucial few words. He also tries to galvanise his imagination - taking a spin of one of the world&apos;s strangest literary board games...

The pressure&apos;s on, as we hear a roll-call of some of the finest and most famous first lines in publishing history - from Dickens to Dostoevsky to uh, Dan Brown. Overwhelmed with information, we also hear a crash course on what not to do - as Tim visits Knebworth House, ancestral pile of a man whose most famous first sentence is legendary for all the wrong reasons: Edward Bulwer-Lytton, author of the infamous &quot;It was a dark and stormy night...&quot;

Finally it&apos;s time to try out Tim&apos;s sentence of the unsuspecting public, as he visits the award-winning Brick Lane Book Club for a focus group...before in the final moments, he unleashes that killer first sentence on the world...(so then Tim: what comes next?).</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0128p3l</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 23:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : The Forgotten Waltz : The Things We Do for Love - Episode 8</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011jv8t</link>
      <description>&apos;The Forgotten Waltz&apos; is Anne Enright&apos;s long-awaited novel, her first since &apos;The Gathering&apos;, which won the Man Booker 2007. 

In a snow blanketed Dublin, Gina reflects on the last decade, from the moment she first caught a glimpse of Sean Vallely, through a haze of cigarette smoke, through the happenstance and lust, the hotel rooms and the secrets, that have brought down two marriages, three mortgages and left her a reluctant inhabitant of her childhood home. Startling, honest, witty and wry, Enright&apos;s novel captures the nuances and the bliss of an overwhelming attraction that becomes an affair and charts the gradual encroachment of reality, damage and a love that can&apos;t be ignored or surpassed. 

In today&apos;s episode Gina realises what she owes to Evie - and what Evie will always have over her. 

The Reader is Niamh Cusack. 
The Abridger is Sally Marmion
The Producer is Di Speirs.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b011jv6w</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 09:07:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : The Forgotten Waltz : Knocking on Heaven&apos;s Door - Episode 7</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011jrhh</link>
      <description>&apos;The Forgotten Waltz&apos; is Anne Enright&apos;s long-awaited novel, her first since &apos;The Gathering&apos;, which won the Man Booker 2007. 

In a snow blanketed Dublin, Gina reflects on the last decade, from the moment she first caught a glimpse of Sean Vallely, through a haze of cigarette smoke, through the happenstance and lust, the hotel rooms and the secrets, that have brought down two marriages, three mortgages and left her a reluctant inhabitant of her childhood home. Startling, honest, witty and wry, Enright&apos;s novel captures the nuances and the bliss of an overwhelming attraction that becomes an affair and charts the gradual encroachment of reality, damage and a love that can&apos;t be ignored or surpassed. 

In today&apos;s episode, Christmas without your lover, and figuring out Evie&apos;s story - and Sean&apos;s heart. 

The Reader is Niamh Cusack. 
The Abridger is Sally Marmion
The Producer is Di Speirs.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b011jrbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 09:10:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : The Forgotten Waltz : Save the Last Dance for Me - Episode 6</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011j81g</link>
      <description>&apos;The Forgotten Waltz&apos; is Anne Enright&apos;s long-awaited novel, her first since &apos;The Gathering&apos;, which won the Man Booker 2007. 

In a snow blanketed Dublin, Gina reflects on the last decade, from the moment she first caught a glimpse of Sean Vallely, through a haze of cigarette smoke, through the happenstance and lust, the hotel rooms and the secrets, that have brought down two marriages, three mortgages and left her a reluctant inhabitant of her childhood home. Startling, honest, witty and wry, Enright&apos;s novel captures the nuances and the bliss of an overwhelming attraction that becomes an affair and charts the gradual encroachment of reality, damage and a love that can&apos;t be ignored or surpassed. 

In today&apos;s episode, the realities of loving a family man, and remembering a father.

The Reader is Niamh Cusack. 
The Abridger is Sally Marmion
The Producer is Di Speirs.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b011j80c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 09:06:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : The Forgotten Waltz : How Can I Be Sure - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011cky1</link>
      <description>&apos;The Forgotten Waltz&apos; is Anne Enright&apos;s long-awaited novel, her first since &apos;The Gathering&apos;, which won the Man Booker 2007. 

In a snow blanketed Dublin, Gina reflects on the last decade, from the moment she first caught a glimpse of Sean Vallely, through a haze of cigarette smoke, through the happenstance and lust, the hotel rooms and the secrets, that have brought down two marriages, three mortgages and left her a reluctant inhabitant of her childhood home. Startling, honest, witty and wry, Enright&apos;s novel captures the nuances and the bliss of an overwhelming attraction that becomes an affair and charts the gradual encroachment of reality, damage and a love that can&apos;t be ignored or surpassed. 

In today&apos;s episode: breaking up and looking back, in the shadow of a For Sale sign, and Dublin&apos;s general disapproval. 

The Reader is Niamh Cusack. 
The Abridger is Sally Marmion
The Producer is Di Speirs.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b011ckv0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2011 09:06:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : The Forgotten Waltz : Dance Me to the End of Love - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011cfyp</link>
      <description>&apos;The Forgotten Waltz&apos; is Anne Enright&apos;s long-awaited novel, her first since &apos;The Gathering&apos;, which won the Man Booker 2007. 

In a snow blanketed Dublin, Gina reflects on the last decade, from the moment she first caught a glimpse of Sean Vallely, through a haze of cigarette smoke, through the happenstance and lust, the hotel rooms and the secrets, that have brought down two marriages, three mortgages and left her a reluctant inhabitant of her childhood home. Startling, honest, witty and wry, Enright&apos;s novel captures the nuances and the bliss of an overwhelming attraction that becomes an affair and charts the gradual encroachment of reality, damage and a love that can&apos;t be ignored or surpassed.

In today&apos;s episode, hotel rooms, the Mistress Game and an unexpected devastation. 

The Reader is Niamh Cusack. 
The Abridger is Sally Marmion
The Producer is Di Speirs.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b011cfnh</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 09:09:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : The Forgotten Waltz : Kiss Me Honey, Honey - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011c248</link>
      <description>&apos;The Forgotten Waltz&apos; is Anne Enright&apos;s long-awaited novel, her first since &apos;The Gathering&apos;, which won the Man Booker 2007. 

In a snow blanketed Dublin, Gina reflects on the last decade, from the moment she first caught a glimpse of Sean Vallely, through a haze of cigarette smoke, through the happenstance and lust, the hotel rooms and the secrets, that have brought down two marriages, three mortgages and left her a reluctant inhabitant of her childhood home. Startling, honest, witty and wry, Enright&apos;s novel captures the nuances and the bliss of an overwhelming attraction that becomes an affair and charts the gradual encroachment of reality, damage and a love that can&apos;t be surpassed or ignored. 

In today&apos;s episode an invitation from his wife to a New Year&apos;s Day party, a stolen kiss and an unwanted witness.

The Reader is Niamh Cusack. 
The Abridger is Sally Marmion
The Producer is Di Speirs.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b011c242</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 09:08:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : The Forgotten Waltz : In These Shoes - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011c0w9</link>
      <description>&apos;The Forgotten Waltz&apos; is Anne Enright&apos;s long-awaited novel, her first since &apos;The Gathering&apos;, which won the Man Booker 2007. 

&apos;The amazing thing is how much I got in that first glance: how much, in retrospect, I should have known. It is all there: the twitch of interest in Sean, the whole business with Evie; I remember this very clearly, as I remember the neat and indomitable politeness of his wife.&apos;

In a snow blanketed Dublin, Gina reflects on the last decade, from the moment she first caught a glimpse of Sean Vallely, through a haze of cigarette smoke, through the happenstance and lust, the hotel rooms and the secrets, that have brought down two marriages, three mortgages and left her a reluctant inhabitant of her childhood home. Startling, honest, witty and wry, Enright&apos;s novel captures the nuances and the bliss of an overwhelming attraction that becomes an affair and charts the gradual encroachment of reality, damage and a love that can&apos;t be overstated. 

In today&apos;s episode an international conference in Switzerland, too much booze and the luxury of the kiss sets lust in motion. 

The Reader is Niamh Cusack. 
The Abridger is Sally Marmion
The Producer is Di Speirs.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b011c0v4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 16:42:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : The Forgotten Waltz : Encounters - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011c0nq</link>
      <description>&apos;The Forgotten Waltz&apos; is Anne Enright&apos;s long-awaited novel, her first since &apos;The Gathering&apos;, which won the Man Booker 2007. 

&apos;The amazing thing is how much I got in that first glance: how much, in retrospect, I should have known. It is all there: the twitch of interest in Sean, the whole business with Evie; I remember this very clearly, as I remember the neat and indomitable politeness of his wife.&apos;

In a snow blanketed Dublin, Gina reflects on the last decade, from the moment she first caught a glimpse of Sean Vallely, through a haze of cigarette smoke, through the happenstance and lust, the hotel rooms and the secrets, that have brought down two marriages, three mortgages and left her a reluctant inhabitant of her childhood home. Startling, honest, witty and wry, Enright&apos;s novel captures the nuances and the bliss of an overwhelming attraction that becomes an affair and charts the gradual encroachment of reality,damage and a love that can&apos;t be overstated. 

. 

The Reader is Niamh Cusack, currently starring in Cause Celebre at the Old Vic. 
The Abridger is Sally Marmion
The Producer is Di Speirs.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b011c0mf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 09:08:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monty Python&apos;s Fliegender Zirkus! - 07/05/2011</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b010y1wr</link>
      <description>Roll up, it&apos;s Monty Python&apos;s Fliegender Zirkus! This is the extraordinary tale of when the Pythons went Bavarian.

German Comedy Ambassador, Henning Wehn, tells the story of how in 1971 the Pythons were flown into Bavaria, full of new original ideas for sketches, including pieces about the German artist Albrecht Durer, William Tell and The Merchant of Venice. They also adapted the popular Flying Circus Lumberjack Song into German and planned to sing it with the Austria Border Police Choir.

Only Michael Palin and John Cleese were capable of delivering lines in &apos;understandable&apos; German. Despite extensive language coaching, Eric Idle, Terry Gilliam, Terry Jones and Graham Chapman were virtually incomprehensible. This may have added to the Pythons&apos; trademark absurdity and surrealism, but was somewhat confusing to the German TV audience.

Realising this dream was becoming a nightmare, Alfred Biokek took the decision to make the second programme in English, with German overdub added later. It proved to be a major hit on German TV, but all concerned decided it best not to repeat the experience.

We hear clips from both programmes and Michael Palin, Terry Jones and Alfred Biolek, the man who persuaded them to take their comedy to Germany, talk about how they came up with the material for the German shows - and how life on set began to imitate a Monty Python sketch.


Producer: Jo Meek
An All Out production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b010y12x</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 10:44:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Obreht - The Tiger&apos;s Wife : Episode 9 - Episode 9</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0100lmv</link>
      <description>Hattie Morahan and David Horovitch read Tea Obreht&apos;s evocative debut novel set in a Balkan country scarred by war, and where Natalia, a young doctor, is struggling to understand the mysterious circumstances of her grandfather&apos;s death. A tattered copy of The Jungle Book which her grandfather kept with him always, provides an unlikely clue, sending her on a quest that leads to the extraordinary stories of an immortal man and the tiger&apos;s wife. Today, Natalia&apos;s grandfather has a further encounter with the deathless man.

Tea Obreht is on &quot;The New Yorker&apos;s Top Writers under 40 Fiction Issue&quot; (June 2010), and at 24 was the youngest on the list. &apos;The Tiger&apos;s Wife&apos; is one of the Waterstone&apos;s 11 - the best debuts that they have picked for 2011. Her short story, &quot;The Sentry&quot;, appeared in the &quot;Guardian Summer Fiction Issue&quot;, alongside stories by Hilary Mantel and David Mitchell.

She was born in 1985 in the former Yugoslavia, and raised in Belgrade, where she spent her childhood. In 1992, her family immigrated, and in 1997 eventually settled in the United States. 

The readers are Hattie Morahan and David Horovitch.


Abridged by Sally Marmion and produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0100lkj</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 12:35:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Obreht - The Tiger&apos;s Wife : Episode 10 - Episode 10</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0100jhd</link>
      <description>Hattie Morahan reads Tea Obreht&apos;s evocative debut novel set in a Balkan country scarred by war, and where Natalia, a young doctor, is struggling to understand the mysterious circumstances of her grandfather&apos;s death. A tattered copy of The Jungle Book which her grandfather kept with him always provides an unlikely clue, sending her on a quest that leads to the extraordinary stories of an immortal man and the tiger&apos;s wife. Today, Natalia makes connections between her father&apos;s childhood, the tiger&apos;s wife and the deathless man.


Tea Obreht is on &quot;The New Yorker&apos;s Top Writers under 40 Fiction Issue&quot; (June 2010), and at 24 was the youngest on the list. &apos;The Tiger&apos;s Wife&apos; is one of the Waterstone&apos;s 11 - the best debuts that they have picked for 2011. Her short story, &quot;The Sentry&quot;, appeared in the &quot;Guardian Summer Fiction Issue&quot;, alongside stories by Hilary Mantel and David Mitchell.

She was born in 1985 in the former Yugoslavia, and raised in Belgrade, where she spent her childhood. In 1992, her family immigrated, and in 1997 eventually settled in the United States. 

The reader is Hattie Morahan. Abridged by Sally Marmion and produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0100jb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 13:31:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Obreht - The Tiger&apos;s Wife : Episode 8 - Episode 8</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0100grn</link>
      <description>Hattie Morahan reads Tea Obreht&apos;s evocative debut novel set in a Balkan country scarred by war, and where Natalia, a young doctor, is struggling to understand the mysterious circumstances of her grandfather&apos;s death. A tattered copy of The Jungle Book which her grandfather kept with him always provides an unlikely clue, sending her on a quest that leads to the extraordinary stories of the deathless man and the tiger&apos;s wife. Today, a bid to save the tiger&apos;s wife has an unwanted outcome.

Ann Patchett has this to say, &quot;The Tiger&apos;s Wife is a marvel of beauty and imagination. Tea Obreht is a tremendously talented writer.&quot;

And T.C. Boyle says, &quot;A novel of surpassing beauty, exquisitely wrought and magical. Tea Obreht is a towering new talent.&quot;

Tea Obreht is on &quot;The New Yorker&apos;s Top Writers under 40 Fiction Issue&quot; (June 2010), and at 24 was the youngest on the list. &apos;The Tiger&apos;s Wife&apos; is one of the Waterstone&apos;s 11 - the best debuts that they have picked for 2011. Her short story, &quot;The Sentry&quot;, appeared in the &quot;Guardian Summer Fiction Issue&quot;, alongside stories by Hilary Mantel and David Mitchell.

She was born in 1985 in the former Yugoslavia, and raised in Belgrade, where she spent her childhood. In 1992, her family immigrated, and in 1997 eventually settled in the United States. 

The reader is Hattie Morahan who has just appeared in Thea Sharrock&apos;s Sheffield Crucible revival of David Hare&apos;s play, &quot;Plenty&quot;. She is well known to television audiences recently playing Miss Enid in Larkrise to Candleford. Radio 4 audiences will have heard her in several radio dramas including, the Classic Serial, &quot;I, Claudius&quot;. Classic Serial.

Abridged by Sally Marmion and produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0100fyr</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 12:58:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Obreht - The Tiger&apos;s Wife : Episode 7 - Episode 7</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0100261</link>
      <description>Hattie Morahan reads Tea Obreht&apos;s evocative debut novel set in a Balkan country scarred by war, and where Natalia, a young doctor, is struggling to understand the mysterious circumstances of her grandfather&apos;s death. A tattered copy of The Jungle Book which her grandfather kept with him always, provides an unlikely clue, sending her on a quest that leads to the extraordinary stories of the deathless man and the tiger&apos;s wife. Today, Natalia returns to the stories of her grandfather&apos;s childhood, and the truth about the failed hunt for the tiger emerges.

Tea Obreht is on &quot;The New Yorker&apos;s Top Writers under 40 Fiction Issue&quot; (June 2010), and at 24 was the youngest on the list. &apos;The Tiger&apos;s Wife&apos; is one of the Waterstone&apos;s 11 - the best debuts that they have picked for 2011. Her short story, &quot;The Sentry&quot;, appeared in the &quot;Guardian Summer Fiction Issue&quot;, alongside stories by Hilary Mantel and David Mitchell.

She was born in 1985 in the former Yugoslavia, and raised in Belgrade, where she spent her childhood. In 1992, her family immigrated, and in 1997 eventually settled in the United States. 

The reader is Hattie Morahan.

Abridged by Sally Marmion and produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b010025x</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 12:40:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Obreht - The Tiger&apos;s Wife : Episode 6 - Episode 6</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00zzz2l</link>
      <description>Hattie Morahan and David Horovitch read Tea Obreht&apos;s evocative debut novel set in a Balkan country scarred by war, and where Natalia, a young doctor, is struggling to understand the mysterious circumstances of her grandfather&apos;s death. A tattered copy of The Jungle Book which her grandfather kept with him always, provides an unlikely clue, sending her on a quest that leads to the extraordinary stories of the deathless man and the tiger&apos;s wife. Today, a miracle leads to a second encounter between Natalia&apos;s grandfather and the deathless man.

Ann Patchett has this to say, &quot;The Tiger&apos;s Wife is a marvel of beauty and imagination. Tea Obreht is a tremendously talented writer.&quot;

And T.C. Boyle says, &quot;A novel of surpassing beauty, exquisitely wrought and magical. Tea Obreht is a towering new talent.&quot;

Tea Obreht is on &quot;The New Yorker&apos;s Top Writers under 40 Fiction Issue&quot; (June 2010), and at 24 was the youngest on the list. &apos;The Tiger&apos;s Wife&apos; is one of the Waterstone&apos;s 11 - the best debuts that they have picked for 2011. Her short story, &quot;The Sentry&quot;, appeared in the &quot;Guardian Summer Fiction Issue&quot;, alongside stories by Hilary Mantel and David Mitchell.

She was born in 1985 in the former Yugoslavia, and raised in Belgrade, where she spent her childhood. In 1992, her family immigrated, and in 1997 eventually settled in the United States. 

The readers are Hattie Morahan and David Horovitch.

Hattie Morahan has just appeared in Thea Sharrock&apos;s Sheffield Crucible revival of David Hare&apos;s play, &quot;Plenty&quot;. She is well known to television audiences recently playing Miss Enid in Larkrise to Candleford. Radio 4 audiences will have heard her in several radio dramas including, the Classic Serial, &quot;I, Claudius&quot;. Classic Serial.

David Horovitch has just appeared in the West End production of When We Are Married.

Abridged by Sally Marmion and produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00zzyqc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 12:58:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Obreht - The Tiger&apos;s Wife : Episode 5 - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00zt611</link>
      <description>Hattie Morahan reads Tea Obreht&apos;s evocative debut novel set in a Balkan country scarred by war, and where Natalia, a young doctor, is struggling to understand the mysterious circumstances of her grandfather&apos;s death. A tattered copy of The Jungle Book which her grandfather kept with him always provides an unlikely clue, sending her on a quest that leads to the extraordinary stories of the deathless man and the tiger&apos;s wife. Today, Natalia evokes her grandfather as a nine year old boy, and the day the men of his village set off to hunt the tiger.

Tea Obreht is on &quot;The New Yorker&apos;s Top Writers under 40 Fiction Issue&quot; (June 2010), and at 24 was the youngest on the list. &apos;The Tiger&apos;s Wife&apos; is one of the Waterstone&apos;s 11 - the best debuts that they have picked for 2011. Her short story, &quot;The Sentry&quot;, appeared in the &quot;Guardian Summer Fiction Issue&quot;, alongside stories by Hilary Mantel and David Mitchell.

She was born in 1985 in the former Yugoslavia, and raised in Belgrade, where she spent her childhood. In 1992, her family immigrated, and in 1997 eventually settled in the United States. 

The reader is Hattie Morahan.
Abridged by Sally Marmion and produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00zt5yd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 15:45:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Obreht - The Tiger&apos;s Wife : Episode 4 - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00zt3tr</link>
      <description>Hattie Morahan reads Tea Obreht&apos;s evocative debut novel set in a Balkan country scarred by war, and where Natalia, a young doctor, is struggling to understand the mysterious circumstances of her grandfather&apos;s death. A tattered copy of The Jungle Book which her grandfather kept with him always provides an unlikely clue, sending her on a quest that leads to the extraordinary stories of the deathless man and the tiger&apos;s wife. Today, the tiger begins his long journey into local legend.

Tea Obreht is on &quot;The New Yorker&apos;s Top Writers under 40 Fiction Issue&quot; (June 2010), and at 24 was the youngest on the list. &apos;The Tiger&apos;s Wife&apos; is one of the Waterstone&apos;s 11 - the best debuts that they have picked for 2011. Her short story, &quot;The Sentry&quot;, appeared in the &quot;Guardian Summer Fiction Issue&quot;, alongside stories by Hilary Mantel and David Mitchell.

She was born in 1985 in the former Yugoslavia, and raised in Belgrade, where she spent her childhood. In 1992, her family immigrated, and in 1997 eventually settled in the United States. 

The reader is Hattie Morahan.
Abridged by Sally Marmion and produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00zt3s2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 15:39:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Obreht - The Tiger&apos;s Wife : Episode 3 - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00zt22l</link>
      <description>Hattie Morahan and David Horovitch read Tea Obreht&apos;s evocative debut novel set in a Balkan country scarred by war, and where Natalia, a young doctor, is struggling to understand the mysterious circumstances of her grandfather&apos;s death. A tattered copy of The Jungle Book which her grandfather kept with him always, provides an unlikely clue, sending her on a quest that leads to the extraordinary stories of the deathless man and the tiger&apos;s wife. Today, memories of a pledge that her grandfather made to the deathless man are conjured up.


Tea Obreht is on &quot;The New Yorker&apos;s Top Writers under 40 Fiction Issue&quot; (June 2010), and at 24 was the youngest on the list. &apos;The Tiger&apos;s Wife&apos; is one of the Waterstone&apos;s 11 - the best debuts that they have picked for 2011. Her short story, &quot;The Sentry&quot;, appeared in the &quot;Guardian Summer Fiction Issue&quot;, alongside stories by Hilary Mantel and David Mitchell.

She was born in 1985 in the former Yugoslavia, and raised in Belgrade, where she spent her childhood. In 1992, her family immigrated, and in 1997 eventually settled in the United States. 

The readers are Hattie Morahan and David Horovitch.

Abridged by Sally Marmion and produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00zt224</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 10:43:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Obreht - The Tiger&apos;s Wife : Episode 2 - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00zshp7</link>
      <description>Hattie Morahan and David Horovitch read Tea Obreht&apos;s evocative debut novel set in a Balkan country scarred by war, and where Natalia, a young doctor, is struggling to understand the mysterious circumstances of her grandfather&apos;s death. A tattered copy of The Jungle Book which her grandfather kept with him always provides an unlikely clue, sending her on a quest that leads to the extraordinary stories of the deathless man and the tiger&apos;s wife. Today, Natalia remembers the night her grandfather told her about his first encounter with the deathless man.


Tea Obreht is on &quot;The New Yorker&apos;s Top Writers under 40 Fiction Issue&quot; (June 2010), and at 24 was the youngest on the list. &apos;The Tiger&apos;s Wife&apos; is one of the Waterstone&apos;s 11 - the best debuts that they have picked for 2011. Her short story, &quot;The Sentry&quot;, appeared in the &quot;Guardian Summer Fiction Issue&quot;, alongside stories by Hilary Mantel and David Mitchell.

She was born in 1985 in the former Yugoslavia, and raised in Belgrade, where she spent her childhood. In 1992, her family immigrated, and in 1997 eventually settled in the United States. 

The readers are Hattie Morahan and David Horovitch.


Abridged by Sally Marmion and produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00zshlz</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 01:09:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Obreht - The Tiger&apos;s Wife : Episode 1 - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00zsdgc</link>
      <description>Hattie Morahan reads Tea Obreht&apos;s evocative debut novel set in a Balkan country scarred by war, and where Natalia, a young doctor, is struggling to understand the mysterious circumstances of her grandfather&apos;s death. A tattered copy of The Jungle Book which her grandfather kept with him always provides an unlikely clue, sending her on a quest that leads to the extraordinary stories of the deathless man and the tiger&apos;s wife.

Tea Obreht is on &quot;The New Yorker&apos;s Top Writers under 40 Fiction Issue&quot; (June 2010), and at 24 was the youngest on the list. &apos;The Tiger&apos;s Wife&apos; is one of the Waterstone&apos;s 11 - the best debuts that they have picked for 2011. Her short story, &quot;The Sentry&quot;, appeared in the &quot;Guardian Summer Fiction Issue&quot;, alongside stories by Hilary Mantel and David Mitchell.

She was born in 1985 in the former Yugoslavia, and raised in Belgrade, where she spent her childhood. In 1992, her family immigrated, and in 1997 eventually settled in the United States. 

The reader is Hattie Morahan.

Abridged by Sally Marmion and produced by Elizabeth Allard.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00zsd8y</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Reading : Womanly Wiles : Mrs Windermere - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00yb2s6</link>
      <description>Elizabeth Bowen&apos;s mysterious story of power and control - as compelling today as when written in 1925.

Two woman - one young, one older - come face to face in the doorway of a Regent Street restaurant. The older woman, Mrs Windermere, grasps Esme&apos;s wrists, draws them towards her bosom, and cries in her deep tremolo, &apos;My dear!&apos; She regards the younger woman with a strange intensity and gently massages the wrists with her thumbs. Unsettling! These two have previously met in Italy. 

But there&apos;s something decidedly odd about Mrs Windermere - her effect on Esme is almost hypnotic. They take a table upstairs and soon Mrs Windermere is discussing Esme&apos;s marriage, and suggesting some surprising changes to her marital status quo. The young woman finds herself being unwillingly drawn in to something peculiar and distasteful. But can she escape the clutches of this strangely controlling personality? 

Reader: Sarah Badel


Producer/Director: Martin Jarvis
A Jarvis &amp; Ayres Production for BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00yb2s0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 01:26:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archive on 4 : Morning Everyone - 13/06/2015</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00pdyfq</link>
      <description>As England continue their Ashes battle against Australia, Rory Bremner looks back on the career of Richie Benaud - the Australian cricketer and commentator whose death earlier this year saw an extraordinary outpouring of love and affection from players, friends and fellow journalists and commentators.
 
Former players talk about his remarkable abilities on the field - as Australia&apos;s leading leg spinner of the 50&apos;s and 60&apos;s, a dogged batsman, and a superb tactician and captain.
 
At the end of his playing career, he turned to journalism and eventually to television presentation and commentary, where he became the undisputed master of understatement. He was once described as the &apos;Sir David Attenborough of Australia&apos;.
 
We hear his recollections, and his own commentaries, of some of the great moments of international cricket - from the 1960 Tied Test to Botham&apos;s Ashes and Edgbaston 2005 - and discuss his love of wine, France and his special role as President of the French Cricket Association.
 
We also touch on his diffidence to those who mimicked his style and delivery - although he did once remark, &quot;Rory Bremner I have no problem with; he is a satirist and a very funny one too&quot;.
 
Produced by Will Yates and David Prest
A Whistledown production, first broadcast on BBC Radio 4.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00pdy6m</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 15:21:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Reading : Alice Munro - Too Much Happiness : Free Radicals - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00p8cph</link>
      <description>Series of short stories from the new collection by Canadian author Alice Munro. 

A newly widowed woman, who is herself dying, is alone in the home she and her husband made their own after she had played the role of &apos;home wrecker&apos; and replaced his first wife. But it is the first wife that she must look to when a stranger threatens at her own kitchen table. 

Read by Barbara Barnes.

Abridged by Sally Marmion.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00p8c1y</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 14:12:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Heart of Saturday Night : Come On Up to the House - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00mbl9q</link>
      <description>&apos;Come On Up to the House&apos;, by acclaimed Scottish writer A L Kennedy, is the first in a series of stories inspired by the distinctive world created by the legendary musician Tom Waits - a dark and sometimes sleazy world peopled by down-at-heel characters on the edge of society, or outcasts singing of loss and longing. In this story, inspired by a Waits track of the same name, a man finds himself reaching out to a perfect stranger in the wee small hours of the morning.

The reader is the acclaimed actor, Peter Capaldi, best known for his film roles in Local Hero and more recently In the Loop, in which he reprised his extraordinary creation, spin doctor Malcolm Tucker from Armando Iannucci&apos;s The Thick of It.

Author: A L Kennedy is a distinguished Scottish author and stand-up comedian who has won awards both for her short stories and novels. In 2003 she was nominated by Granta magazine as one of 20 &apos;Best of Young British Novelists&apos;.

Produced by Justine Willett.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00mbl72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:17:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary Wesley - The Camomile Lawn : Episode 10 - Episode 10</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0080sjp</link>
      <description>A funeral sparks a big reunion of old faces at the house in Cornwall. Sian Phillips concludes the family saga.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0080sj9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 13:33:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary Wesley - The Camomile Lawn : Episode 9 - Episode 9</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0080qtn</link>
      <description>Max gets a telephone call about Monica, while Helena gets a surprise visitor. Read by Sian Phillips.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0080qs7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 13:10:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary Wesley - The Camomile Lawn : Episode 8 - Episode 8</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0080qbv</link>
      <description>Sophie has an accident, Polly tries to forget, and Calypso gets news. Read by Sian Phillips.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0080qbj</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 12:44:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary Wesley - The Camomile Lawn : Episode 7 - Episode 7</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0080p26</link>
      <description>Calypso pays a visit to Polly, and discovers her unusual relationship with the twins. Read by Sian Phillips.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0080p1p</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 13:36:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary Wesley - The Camomile Lawn : Episode 6 - Episode 6</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0080jj1</link>
      <description>Sophie tells all, and Calypso has a secret for Hector, but where is he? Sian Phillips reads the Second World War family saga.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0080jht</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 10:58:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary Wesley - The Camomile Lawn : Episode 5 - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00807gp</link>
      <description>Helena leaves her lover to help Richard. A gun shot causes a commotion. Read by Sian Phillips.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00807g4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 13:20:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary Wesley - The Camomile Lawn : Episode 4 - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00805nd</link>
      <description>The cousins&apos; relationships blossom in London, but the Second World War starts to take its toll. Read by Sian Phillips.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00805mz</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 12:17:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary Wesley - The Camomile Lawn : Episode 3 - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00804b2</link>
      <description>As Calypso weds wealthy Scotsman Hector Grant, the other cousins must move on. Read by Sian Phillips.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b008049h</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 12:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary Wesley - The Camomile Lawn : Episode 2 - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00803g6</link>
      <description>As the sirens sound for the Second World War, Monica has good reason to be worried. Read by Sian Phillips.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00803fj</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 11:55:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary Wesley - The Camomile Lawn : Episode 1 - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00801nd</link>
      <description>A Cornish house with a fragrant lawn links five cousins through war and adulthood. Read by Sian Phillips.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b00801lz</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 11:34:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Reading : William Trevor - Cheating at Canasta : Cheating at Canasta - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007x286</link>
      <description>Mallory dines alone at a favourite restaurant in Venice and eavesdrops on the couple at the next table. Read by William Trevor.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b007x21p</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 18:25:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Reading : William Trevor - Cheating at Canasta : The Dressmaker&apos;s Child - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007x23g</link>
      <description>Cahal&apos;s plans to dupe a gullible young couple backfire tragically. Read by the author, William Trevor.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b007x22v</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 18:28:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Reading : William Trevor - Cheating at Canasta : The Children - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007x23f</link>
      <description>As her father plans to remarry, Connie fights to honour a love as important as her father&apos;s new one. Read by William Trevor.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b007x22h</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 18:27:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Reading : William Trevor - Cheating at Canasta : Old Flame - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007x23d</link>
      <description>William Trevor reads stories from his new collection.

Zoe&apos;s marriage has been haunted by Audrey, with whom her husband once had an affair, and also Grace. But Grace is now dead.

Abridged by Sally Marmion.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b007x21z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 18:26:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Reading : William Trevor - Cheating at Canasta : Folie a Deux - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007x07y</link>
      <description>A chance meeting in Paris revives powerful memories of a shared past on an Irish beach. Story collection read by William Trevor.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b007x07g</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 18:21:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedy Greats : The Nineties : Episode 1 - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007k35z</link>
      <description>Decade by decade, Barry Cryer showcases some of the funniest and finest shows ever broadcast by the BBC. 

Yo! Well wicked Baz presents six fave shows plucked from the 1990s schedules of BBC Radio 4 and BBC Radio 5:- 

*  A Look Back At The Nineties
(2/5) 1996:
Recorded in 1993 - Brian Perkins, Kate Robbins and Chris Barrie &quot;look back&quot; at the decade that was yet to happen. 

*  Hair in the Gate
Series 1 (3/6) 
Camilla revamps the TV arts show to keep her cutting edge lover. Stars Harriet Thorpe and Alistair McGowan. From 1993. 


*  The Now Show
Series 3 (4/13)
Steve Punt and Hugh Dennis poke fun at events of 1999 via sketches, songs and stand-up. With Bert Tyler-Moore, George Jeffrie, Mitch Benn and Marcus Brigstocke.

*  Goodness Gracious Me
Series 3 (6/6)
&apos;The Archers&apos; and &apos;The Waltons&apos; with a twist and The Minx Twins tackle feminism. Stars Sanjeev Bhaskar, Meera Syal, Nina Wadia and Kulvinder Ghir. From 1998. 

*  On The Town With The League of Gentlemen
(4/6)  Gunpowder, Treason and Plot
The eccentric locals of the town of Spent get an unusual new guy for the bonfire. Pre-TV sitcom with Steve Pemberton, Mark Gatiss and Reece Shearsmith. From 1997.

*  On The Hour
Series 2 (5/6)
Ireland hits the headlines, as the programme celebrates its 33rd birthday. Chris Morris fronts the news satire. With Steve Coogan, David Schneider, Rebecca Front, Doon Mackichan and Patrick Marber. From 1992. 

Produced and scripted by Peter Reed 

First broadcast on BBC 7 in 2003.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b0070526</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 15:50:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fay Weldon Stories : I, Boadicea - 17/12/2006</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007jzwj</link>
      <description>The formidable queen of history speaks of the rages and battles she undertook for her people. Read by Vanessa Redgrave.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b006ntf8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 09:52:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rukhsana Ahmad - Freedom&apos;s Daughter : Episode 5 - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007jybp</link>
      <description>Nehru is released from jail, while Indira Gandhi&apos;s political views are developing. Read by Nina Wadia. and Paul Bhattacharjee.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b006lty1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 01:26:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rukhsana Ahmad - Freedom&apos;s Daughter : Episode 4 - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007jy99</link>
      <description>Nehru feels cut off from Indira, as tragic events threaten to overtake his family. Read by Nina Wadia. and Paul Bhattacharjee.</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b006ltw2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 01:21:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Purple Hibiscus : Episode 10 - Episode 10</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0076qfv</link>
      <description>Jaja has been imprisoned for Papa&apos;s murder. But his release is near, and Kambili plans a future of love, laughter - and purple hibiscus.

Read by Rakie Ayola 
Abridged by Sarah LeFanu</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b005qzp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:48:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Purple Hibiscus : Episode 9 - Episode 9</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0076qfb</link>
      <description>A shock for Kambili - both Aunty Ifeoma and Father Amadi are leaving Nigeria. A pilgrimage lifts her spirits, but then there is horrific news.

Read by Rakie Ayola 
Abridged by Sarah LeFanu</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b005qzbt</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:48:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Purple Hibiscus : Episode 8 - Episode 8</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0076qdr</link>
      <description>Kambili is recovering with Aunty Ifeoma and her cousins. More violence is to come at home, but the purple hibiscuses are about to bloom.

Read by Rakie Ayola 
Abridged by Sarah LeFanu</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b005qz7h</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:47:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Purple Hibiscus : Episode 7 - Episode 7</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0076qd6</link>
      <description>Violence is spreading under Nigeria&apos;s new military rulers. At home, Papa loses all control, and nearly kills Kambili.

Read by Rakie Ayola 
Abridged by Sarah LeFanu</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b005qz14</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:45:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Purple Hibiscus : Episode 6 - Episode 6</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0076qcn</link>
      <description>Papa&apos;s &apos;heathen&apos; father has died in Aunty Ifeoma&apos;s flat. Now Kambili and Jaja feel Papa&apos;s wrath.

Read by Rakie Ayola 
Abridged by Sarah LeFanu</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b005qyvq</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:45:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Purple Hibiscus : Episode 5 - Episode 5</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0076qbh</link>
      <description>Kambili learns about her grandfather&apos;s &apos;heathen&apos; beliefs, and Father Amadi teaches her to smile.

Read by Rakie Ayola
Abridged by Sarah LeFanu</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b005qrvh</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:41:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Purple Hibiscus : Episode 4 - Episode 4</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0076qb0</link>
      <description>A visit to Aunty Ifeoma introduces Kambili and her brother Jaja to a life without fear - and to the rare purple hibiscus.

Read by Rakie Ayola
Abridged by Sarah LeFanu</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b005qrj0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Purple Hibiscus : Episode 3 - Episode 3</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0076q9f</link>
      <description>It&apos;s Christmas, and Kambili and her brother are about to visit their grandfather and aunt.

Read by Rakie Ayola
Abridged by Sarah LeFanu</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b005qrd5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:41:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Purple Hibiscus : Episode 2 - Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0076q8x</link>
      <description>Kambili, distressed by her mother&apos;s miscarriage, is struggling to revise for exams, while a military coup threatens Papa&apos;s businesses.

Read by Rakie Ayola
Abridged by Sarah LeFanu</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b005qr3v</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:34:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book at Bedtime : Purple Hibiscus : Episode 1 - Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0076q8d</link>
      <description>Mama has at last become pregnant, but Papa&apos;s violence erupts, and Kambili&apos;s ordered world starts to fall apart.

Read by Rakie Ayola
Abridged by Sarah LeFanu</description>
      <category>Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPID;b005qr0q</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:34:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>